Good afternoon, lovely people.
I love you all.
I gotta wait a little bit.
The coffee is brewing.
It's gonna be nice and piping hot.
So I gotta leave.
It takes about 40 minutes or so.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
It's a special setup I have going on.
It's going through three layers of people as well.
It's quite something.
It's a slow machine, but it really produces the best.
You know, maybe it's overkill to hire three people for that, but I think coffee is worth it.
Cheers in a moment or in 40 minutes.
Oh man, guys, I have made some decisions in my life.
It sounds dramatic or something.
It's not.
It's just about gaming.
I think we're gonna be playing more games.
I crossed the board.
More games.
No bacon, but more games.
What does that mean with the bacon and the games?
You know what I mean?
Unlimited games.
Except that's the one.
Unlimited games, but no more bacon.
I was thinking maybe Factorio on stream as well.
We can do both, you know?
Maybe turn Isaac into a...
because this game, I'm gonna be playing Isaac for a while, guys.
I think this is the perfect game, and someone mentioned this.
It is the perfect game to just have and go back to occasionally.
You know what I mean?
Like, because this is something I think about all the time.
Isaac is the game that I can always play, I think.
And then for YouTube, I'm thinking about a couple games right now.
Potentially, I'm not gonna say it actually.
I don't want to say too much, because if I end up not liking it, then I don't really want to reveal that I played it, I guess.
Because I'm not gonna put out episodes of it, right?
That's the plan, at least.
Let's just say maybe I'll try out some bigger games.
Some different games.
Shorter games as well.
Unlimited games.
Maybe.
Some of you got it.
E33 Incident Aware.
It's kind of an unfortunate one with E33.
Normally, I wouldn't have uploaded that, but I actually convinced myself that I was gonna play it again.
And maybe it was me just coping, but I think deep inside, I knew that I So in a way, I was lying more to myself, you know?
Like, yeah, sure, I'll pick it up, but I never did.
So, yeah, I totally fucked up with that one.
Definitely.
Rimworld is a great idea as well.
Hold on a minute, I'm gonna go grab my coffee.
I lied about the 40 minutes.
It's four minutes.
I am so freaking ready.
Have you played Disco Elysium?
I have.
I played it before it got full voiceover.
And I think I actually got lucky with that because I really enjoyed imagining the voices in my head while reading it.
I saw a couple scenes from the game, memorable scenes for me at least, that just weren't hitting as hard as before they put voices to the characters.
Because I had, you know, imagined the most funny situation ever with the funniest voices in my head while playing.
And it just wasn't quite the same with the voices, you know?
So I think I got the perfect experience of the game.
Great suggestion though.
Can I ask if you're gonna update the Ultimate Video Game Tier List?
It's been almost exactly a year now.
Yeah, but I haven't played that many games since.
I'm kind of slow, you know?
I can't spam games too hard.
But maybe I will.
Because Unlimited Games.
Unlimited Games.
You ever thought about watching shows on your side channel?
But I can't.
I wish I could do stuff like that.
There's nothing I would do more or would want to do more than watch shows with you guys.
That would be so much fun.
Oh yeah, Infinite Games.
Wait, was it Unlimited Games or Infinite Games?
I think Unlimited was the one, right?
You can record your reaction without showing the show.
Yeah, but it's not really the same, you know?
Then you would have to have the exact same show open and then synchronize.
I don't know, man.
I don't know about that.
Streaming on Discord?
Yeah, but that doesn't make me any money.
The whole point behind that would be, you know, to incorporate it into the way I make money.
This is how I make money now.
I am full-time streaming, right?
How do all the other channels get by with this?
I don't know.
Do they?
Do they actually stream the show?
I'm pretty sure that's not allowed.
Other players get to work.
I mean, I'm working right now.
I'm talking to you guys.
I think that's part of it.
Some people do, but how are they getting away with that?
If I upload just an inkling of anything that smells of a copyright, I immediately get claimed.
I can't even imagine uploading anything remotely close to a show or a movie.
That would be crazy.
Have you been to Italy?
I have.
It's one of my favorite countries of all time.
Beautiful landscapes on incredible food.
It's just the best.
Lovely people.
It's so nice there.
Except mosquitoes.
During the summer months.
Jackie Chan is in fan art.
That's exactly what I imagined, Nikki.
That is perfect.
That's wonderful.
I love how she looks so bewildered.
Like, she's not quite sure that she was able to do that.
That's funny.
I have watched The Expanse.
It's a fantastic show.
Really loved it.
I need more sci-fi shows.
Guys, I actually just started a new show called Rectify.
Highly recommended.
I've only watched two episodes so far, but man, that shit's good.
Really good.
Never heard of it before, and then I just stumbled on it.
Rectify is what it's called.
Highly recommended from me.
Who knows?
Maybe it takes a nosedive later, but so far?
Very good.
I've not watched Castlevania or Deep Space 9.
But I have watched... What is it called?
Battlestar Galactica.
I love that show.
It's a little corny at times, but you know.
It's a good time.
I love Gaius.
My favorite character.
Hey, what's up?
Giwuri from Italy.
Love your content.
I love your country.
Thank you.
I think I watched Teletubbies as a kid.
I thought it was creepy.
There's the sun in the sky, you know, with a face and...
Yeah, I don't know, man.
When you think about all those kids shows, they're super creepy.
We are playing Isaac today, yes.
We are sacking it up.
Good old sacking.
Three days in a row?
Yeah, red just do, as some of the comments said.
No, I also want to play Isaac.
I actually started some new medicine against the shit on my face that I've been having trouble with for almost a year now.
And four days into the medicine, it's already helping a lot compared to everything else I've tried.
So I'm in a really good mood because of that.
Like, it's crazy how much of a downer it is to go through that.
It really fucks with my life in so many ways, in ways you don't even realize.
But now that it seems to be working, I've already gained so much more motivation in my day-to-day, you know?
Health up pills, exactly.
And that's without the PhD.
Okay, Jackie is once again jumping on the table, which is weird.
I don't know why she starts doing this.
I played with her a little before I started this stream, just to, you know, satisfy her play cravings so I can stream in peace.
Man, she probably just heard about me talking about Isaac, you know?
She wants a part of it.
Jackie's so cute.
Okay, let's play some Isaac.
Let's see here.
We're not gonna do voting today, we're just gonna do varied gameplay.
I'm gonna do a bit of everything, I promise.
We're gonna speedrun, we're gonna do Lazarus, yep.
We're gonna do some randomization, some greed, and challenge.
Uh, wait, why are my audios not showing up?
Oh, there they are, okay.
Isaac.
Isaac!
Oh, minus four!
Whoo!
I don't want to look at that.
Wait, I wonder what... Hmm.
Have I been fucking up all this time not playing normal?
Why am I actually playing hard?
Is there a difference at all between...
Look at all the, uh, achievements thingies I have on Azazel.
Four, five in total.
I have heart, uh, cross, upside down, star.
I forgot what that was.
Uh, the scent is definitely greed mode.
The star.
It could be the 15 waves.
What the hell is that?
On Eve, I have a square with another square inside.
I don't have that on any other character.
What did I do on Eve?
I don't know.
Okay, let's do Lazarus on heart.
I'm gonna try and unlock, uh, who was it?
Bethany.
Doesn't Bethany look like, uh, the villain from the Dark Knight Rises?
What's his name?
The guy who... Who looks like this?
You know what I mean?
A little bit?
Am I crazy?
I expect you to die.
I can't do his voice.
Okay.
Lazarus, you glorious bastard.
We're gonna make this happen.
You and I.
Excellent.
Beautiful.
Get it out of your system before we get it started here.
We can't die.
No keys.
No drinks.
Can't do it.
Why am I blowing this up?
Oh, look at this!
Did that rock right next to explosive?
My luck is unmatched.
That is actually fantastic.
Oh, there goes my perfection.
I am not perfect, guys.
I am simply amazing.
I'll have to settle with amazing.
That's okay.
I don't ask for much.
And there's the boss already.
I don't approve.
We need to get the treasure first.
And also a key, perhaps.
That would bring me happiness.
I'm hiding.
Ah, okay.
Do not go back and forth.
This is a new rule.
If you do drive bys, keep running in a circle.
Also, my mouse pad is in the way again.
There we go.
Treasure room acquired.
I don't even know what that item is.
I don't think I've had that before.
It looks different.
Tractor beam.
Plus one tears, range and shot speed.
And that's a beam from i6 face.
Tears travel within the beam.
Ah, that's the one.
Yeah, okay.
I've had this before.
That's actually pretty good.
Let me double check something here.
Changing direction instantly relocates.
Right.
Nice.
No money though.
You could actually like do this and then go around the corner and immediately have a bunch of tears.
Coupon.
I see a lot of coupons lately.
You know what else?
Just having the blue laser is actually kind of nice just for aiming.
It's nice to see exactly where my shots are going.
Especially now that it's guaranteed they fall along the laser, right?
That is actually massive.
The only problem is I can't shoot diagonally anymore.
But that's okay.
I don't mind.
You know what I need now?
Shot speed.
I think shot speed is a great combo with the tractor beam.
I definitely could have played this floor better.
Let me see here.
Oh actually let's let's step a little bit.
I feel blessed.
Who knows?
Maybe uh you know we could have gotten a coin or something.
Oh we have a tinted rock here.
I don't think my bomb is gonna reach that unfortunately.
Oh it's only two rocks.
Let me actually confirm.
We're gonna test this once and for all.
Okay it's only two rocks.
Now wait how's this gonna work with the tractor beam?
This needs to be experimented with.
Isn't that weird?
Steven.
Let me try and miss with it.
I don't think it does anything actually.
I think uh this is over uh the tractor beam is overriding.
Yeah.
Oh you're mad now.
Oh you're fast.
Kill the small guy I guess.
Getting a little risky here.
Would love to find some hp now.
That way I can get healed and also get another.
Whoa that was close.
Okay you know what?
I think every time you find Steven this is guaranteed to spawn.
You get this no matter what and that's nice.
Damage is welcome.
I enjoy it.
Cheers.
Nice hot coffee.
100% demon mode.
Always on the second floor.
Oi oi oi.
Are you gonna poop with me?
You tried to.
Oh shit.
I'm actually kind of in danger here.
I need healing.
Oh let's be careful.
You know what?
I think I should blow him up actually.
Yeah.
Tears are 50% wider.
Oh that's really good.
I like that.
No key though.
Oh shit.
I'm actually kind of in danger.
That is huge.
That just saved the run I think.
Ultimate saved the run.
I don't deserve it.
What have I done to deserve this luck?
Man being able to just go back and forth like this, it's kind of good.
I like the tractor beam.
Huge fan of it.
Nice.
I do need a key though.
That's very important.
Ah yeah.
Full health.
Not bad.
Wait we're at 71% demon.
Something happened.
Today I will figure out the freaking doors by the way.
The door to a fight club will be figured out today.
I think if I say it out loud it's gonna happen.
I can will it into existence.
It has been a mystery for two damn long.
So watch this.
I'm gonna go like this and then immediately turn it.
Not that it helped a lot but you know the idea was there.
Let's look for tinted rocks.
I got a bomb.
Nothing in here.
Boss already.
I mean I have full health.
Maybe not a bad idea.
I have good damage.
Yeah.
Dingle me up son.
I'm single and ready to dingle.
You gonna charge me?
No you're not.
Kill the little guy.
How did I ever lose to this guy?
Because I remember losing to him.
He's mega easy.
Tropicamete.
Tear size increase.
Bro these tears are gonna be massive.
And you know what?
Hold on a minute.
I realized something just now.
Last dream I was definitely making a lot of dumb mistakes.
Because every time I made a mistake immediately after I was like fuck.
How could that have happened?
You know like leaving behind an important item or missing something obvious that I really needed to survive.
And then I ended up dying.
Not today.
I have done some soul searching.
Some intro-spective things.
And I think I have become a changed man.
I don't miss small things anymore.
Or big things.
Small things are okay to miss.
Because it's small.
But you'll see I'm a changed man.
And it starts with Lazarus.
I need this key.
You better give me this key or I'm gonna cry.
You can't let me go without the treasure room.
Can these spawn keys?
I don't know.
I'm scared.
That's a heart.
Okay.
Give me a key please.
I could maybe get a key if I blow something up.
Let me have a look here.
Or we look for a secret.
That is another option.
Imagine if the secret room is here we can get access to the treasure room.
Let's gamble.
Shit.
Okay.
That's one gamble.
We can't afford to do any... Oh wait!
There's a rock here!
Look at that!
Totally missed that!
Nice!
It's okay.
I'm just not gonna get my my key I guess.
This was guaranteed, you know?
Uh, can't get that either.
Yeah.
Oh, we can go into the curse room.
Why not?
I'll sacrifice a blue heart for that.
Gladly.
Spawns a beggar?
He could give me a key!
Just don't take all my money, okay?
Don't take all my money!
Good, sir?
Yeah!
Great start!
Okay, I don't even care about the treasure room anymore.
We're golden.
Fabulous.
I love that when he gives me the item he just blasts off, you know?
My people need me.
Here we go!
Let me try and think, what would I like to get with my tractor beam?
I would like to get more tears and more shot speed.
Well, I think everyone wants that no matter what they have, but you know.
Just saying.
I think I especially want that now.
Okay, so this area is actually one of my favorite areas, but it's also one of the most dangerous ones.
The enemies here are crazy.
Let's start seeing more murdering.
These shoot diagonal, yeah.
What is that room?
What do we have here?
Is that a planetarium?
I'm excited.
I don't know what it is, but I'm excited.
Wait, I think I just fucked up.
I can't get that key.
Shit.
I need a key.
I need a key real bad now.
Give me that.
Surely I'll find a key, right?
Oh, that hit me.
Come on, come on.
I think if I blow this up it should...
Yeah, okay, never mind.
I was wrong.
I could put a bomb here, though, and get four coins.
Right before the... but I don't have a key for this.
And we're not gonna do it.
Dude, my tears are actually kind of big.
Very nice.
Shit, I was hoping we would get into the new room.
Too bad.
Solid.
I don't think I'm gonna blow those flames up, not yet.
Yeah, now aiming and, you know, staying on target is more about my movement, and not so much about shooting the projectiles in the right angle.
It's just about staying aligned with the enemy.
Just kind of nice.
Hematemesis.
Wait, what did that do?
It took away my HP and then gave it back to me?
Did I note that down?
Hematemesis.
No, I didn't.
Or maybe I removed it.
Fuck.
I did remove some of them, thinking, ah, I'll remember that.
We don't need to note it down.
Maybe that was a mistake.
Get him out of here.
Okay, come on.
A key!
We're going to the new room.
New room, baby.
Let's see it.
Looking for tinted rocks on the way.
I could also maybe get that key, if I get flying.
Yeah, here.
Ooh, this has to be the planetarium!
Oh,
teleport to the treasure room.
If there is a planetarium, teleport to it instead.
And the shop.
Wait, do we even have it?
We do have a shop.
Oh, nice!
We can get inside without using a key.
HP up, plus you feel pretty?
Applies charm to enemies in close range.
Oh, nice!
That's really good.
Let's take this one first.
Music was nice in there.
I wonder why that...
Did I just get super lucky or what?
Uh, humbling bundle.
Oh, I'm good here.
I'm good.
Although I could get four more coins, if I needed.
So now we can teleport to the treasure room.
Ah, but wait!
There's a planetarium, so we should be teleporting here, right?
Yeah, shit.
Tell me I can get inside the treasure room.
What is this cruel fate?
Twice in a row I can't get in there?
It's okay.
This is... I'm now a changed man, so that's not gonna affect me mentally.
We're gonna take those and we're gonna see the silver lining.
The silver lining behind that is, I'm gonna play more cautious now.
Because I don't have all these amazing items that I normally would have had, right?
And I'm gonna win, therefore.
Shit!
Maybe I can find a secret somewhere.
Oh, you know what?
There's probably a secret nestled in between that square of rooms over there.
Let me double check from every angle, so we go in here.
This could work.
Let me check the north.
Could work!
And what about... oh, but what about this?
This is like some different plane we're on.
It may not work in that case.
Let me uh, let me try here.
Shit!
Okay, but here though, we're gonna gain access into the treasure room from here.
Trust!
Last bomb.
Silver lining.
Think happy thoughts.
Everything is fine.
It's okay.
Here we go.
Did I say 100% demon?
Yeah, we're 100% demon, baby!
Love it!
Are you gonna charge me or what?
Mine is 99% demon!
Okay, taking damage is definitely reducing that.
I think we can confirm that definitively now.
Sir, will you come out from there?
It's tied to the perfection, I think, in some way.
Like, rich get richer, you know?
Dude, what are you doing?
Oh, wait, you're char... oh, you're charmed?
I'm not even gonna attack the spider next to me.
Oh, now I am.
Nice.
Cube of meat.
I'll take it.
Well, there goes my devil chance, but you know what?
Silver lining.
We're taking angels!
We're not gonna go with the demons.
Happy thoughts.
It's angel time!
Now, dad!
Yes, we shall pray until your hands bleed.
Finally, we get a key.
That hurt a little bit.
Okay, not bad.
Secondhand increases the duration of status effects.
No, I like the current one.
Having big old tears makes me big old happy.
Yeah, look at them!
We're gonna charm them and they're gonna go to war for us.
Go to war!
If I find the poop active, I'm definitely getting it.
Or the fart one.
Actually one of the best actives.
Playing mega safe.
Go to war.
Sweet.
Tropicamide in your ass.
Come here.
Oh, that was weirdly easy.
How come they were running away from me?
Because they weren't charmed.
That was a sick reaction.
Yeah, why not?
Bring it on, fatty.
I will jiggle that tummy of yours.
Oh, he's pulling in that?
That's that's good for me.
Take damage.
Come on.
Let me just walk around.
No problem.
Actually, the more I move, the more the...
Oh, never mind.
Actually, I was wrong.
I was about to say the more I move, the more the projectiles spread.
So if I move slower, I can sort of control the projectiles.
But that's not how this works.
Not this guy at least.
Oh, that is incredible.
We are getting so lucky right now.
I am gonna step for sure.
This is a step run.
Let's go find a step room.
And potentially some healing.
And we have a key, so let's save it for the treasure room.
Become my friend.
What's that?
I mean, that's pretty good.
But not that good.
Oh, here we go.
Definitely going in here.
Kill each other.
I can give this guy some HP.
Why not?
I'm down for that.
Okay, not too much now.
I need something in return.
Okay, well, let me do it there in case I need to blow both of you up at the same time.
I think I will give you one more.
One more.
Okay, come on, please be good.
I mean, that's okay.
Oh, wait.
Thank God I didn't go down to half a health.
I would have died if I went out, right?
Maybe I can get some HP here.
Oh, invested.
Okay.
Show me some good stuff.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Take it.
That's gonna safeguard my exit.
Money's there to be used, right?
Shit.
Okay, we're gonna blow them up.
Pills have been acquired.
If this is health down, that's fine.
Oh, yeah.
Dude, we are so rich on health.
Let's go collect the other red hearts.
And the best part is, if we find another health up, we're gonna see it, right?
It's gonna be revealed to us.
Okay, I don't have that much healing.
This is not that great.
I wonder if it's the developer of the game who makes those sounds or who speaks, you know?
I feel like I should make my own mod for this game.
I was inspired by the gym button, right?
Imagine I make my own mod and I replace every sound effect with my own made with my mouth.
So, every time I shoot, I go... or something.
And when I find a power up, I go, yes, power up.
I think that would be funny.
Okay, so wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on, hold on.
It's closed.
There's no blue flames.
Let me just double check this one more time.
Okay, it's not a bomb.
Notice this is the one with the skull on it.
So, maybe that is different.
What is happening right now?
We have minus one lock.
Maybe we need to be above zero lock.
That could be a thing.
It could be somehow tied to devils or angels.
Um, maybe it could also be related to perfection.
How perfect I've been playing.
Those three options make sense to me.
We're gonna try and root it out today.
We're gonna exclude and do some actual testing.
Yeah, you guys are my friends now.
I gotta be really careful here.
Every health is valuable right now.
Even though I have a lot, I have very little.
Oh, thank you, mushroom.
Okay, you've charged so you can't do it again.
Not yet.
Okay, there we go.
Beautiful.
Help me up.
Nothing.
Okay, I could blow up mushrooms.
Trying to get lucky with that, but that's a bit risky.
Go for him.
Shit.
Oh, the key is wonderful.
Oh wait, we have a full heart in the boss room.
I didn't even see that.
I'm going back for it.
That is a must.
It's a little too risky right now, what I'm doing.
We're almost just playing like Judas right now.
There it is.
Much better.
That just reduced chances of losing by 50%.
At least.
Also, you may notice I'm not speedrunning at all right now.
That's on purpose.
I'm going super slow.
Because this is about unlocking a character, and that's important.
Nice.
What the hell is that?
Oh, sick!
It's an active...
Whoa, we're gonna get a lot of HP, baby.
I could also re-roll it, but I don't think I want... then again.
Hold on a minute, maybe I want to re-roll it.
Now, I only have two coins.
I only have two coins, so it wouldn't be worth it.
Speaking of only two coins, I should probably not enter there then.
Yeah, let's leave.
I'm gonna save my keys.
I can't possibly be anything in there that's worth my time when I don't have money for it, right?
Now, this is me making a smart decision, and I'm proud of myself for that right now.
I held back.
Okay.
Eternal heart!
Grant me, sucker!
Here we go.
Dank depths.
And it's not that dark, thankfully.
Sometimes this place is really dark.
Oh, am I glad that's my friend right now?
Kill each other!
Nice.
Oh, god.
Yeah, go for it, go for it.
Murder each other.
Yes.
Oh, that's some creep right there.
I don't like that.
Get away from me.
Dude, you are so annoying.
The tractor beam makes this really hard.
Shit!
Okay.
Nice.
I still gotta play really careful here.
I'm still low on HP.
Man, the tractor beam is so good.
Where do you think you're going?
Professional.
Oh!
Love this one!
Okay, so you heard it, right?
There is one door, and it could be related to up in the heavens, right?
I think we may have to go up this time.
Then again, I have been up quite a bit.
And I gotta, you know, murder Satan.
That bastard deserves a spanking, for lack of a better word.
I'm not very good at dealing with him, which is an argument to deal with him more, you know, to learn it.
Okay.
Man, keys are no problem anymore.
Nice.
Weird room, though.
I need my treasure room.
Very poor this run.
South.
Like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, kill each other!
Nerds.
Kill him, kill him.
That's right, that's how you do it.
I'm not gonna grab that coin.
Kill each other.
I think I've started to really appreciate the status effects like charm and, you know, all the others.
Purple hearts.
Yeah.
Ah, but then my tears are smaller.
But I do like purple heart.
Increases chance of encountering champion enemies, and 50% chance for champions to drop their special loot, and it's doubled as well.
I mean, we need that, right?
Wow.
Wow!
Close one.
Wait, we're not leaving yet, though.
What about my treasure room?
Ah, you were charmed!
How dare you?
Hey, these guys are trapped.
Wait, what?
What if you don't have a bomb here?
What do you do?
Ah, okay, they relocate.
I see.
Does this guy relocate, though?
Uh-huh.
Oh my god!
I can get a heart right now!
Hey!
Not bad!
That means we can potentially get another one at the end of this level, if we get enough energy.
I don't think so, though.
That's a lot of battery we need.
We could find a battery, though.
Maybe in the shop there's a battery?
It could be.
What?
You hit me.
I didn't even see that tile.
This guy's gonna jump at me soon, so I'm just gonna take him out.
I don't like when they jump.
Here we go.
Oh, that's a good one!
This is such a good synergy with all my red hearts.
So nice.
What's up, buddy?
Let's go on adventures together.
I'll be grabbing this.
Then we're going north.
In fact, I should just let this guy finish off everyone now.
As much as I can.
Okay, we can start damaging you a little bit and then I'm gonna let him finish you.
Okay, kill him now.
I believe in you.
Yeah!
Sick.
Okay, that's fine.
Go to the shop, maybe?
We could find a battery there on sale, imagine.
There is a chance.
And a chance smells good.
Oh no, we can't get it.
Unless...
Yeah.
There we go, baby.
That's another guaranteed eternal heart.
Not bad, huh?
Combined with my leech.
Oh, we're gonna do great things.
Monstro the second.
I'm gonna let leech finish him off.
If I can.
Oh god.
I'm gonna jump.
That's cool.
Gonna jump again.
Oh man, I should have seen that coming.
I'm actually kind of playing bad here.
I admit.
Oh my goodness.
Dude, okay, calm down, calm down, calm down, calm
down.
You're kidding!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Oh wait, uh, oh wait, oh uh, wait.
I want to grab that heart.
I don't want to jump down though.
Oh no, kill these.
Don't hit me now, don't hit me now.
Okay, uh, some kind of nail and Ouija board.
Spectral tears is actually great.
I'm taking both.
I have so many hearts.
Why wouldn't I just take both?
Oh, it's an active.
Damage up and speed down for the current room.
Okay, deal contact damage while active.
Can break rocks by walking into them while active.
Activation grants half a black heart.
Whoa, okay.
That sounds really good actually.
I may just use this now and take the other.
Yeah, we're moving on with this one.
This sounds cool.
Nice, I could grab it and we're going.
Very nice.
Let's really experiment with this.
Also, it's mom time.
We're keeping track of all those things.
Let me read this again.
So damage up but speed down.
It's probably going to be really slow then.
Contact damage can break rocks and it grants half a black heart.
What?
So that means, yo, that means I activated.
I walk into an enemy.
I take damage and everyone dies in the room because the black heart gets consumed.
Whoa.
Let me try that.
Hit me.
Yeah.
Actually insane combo.
Very nice.
Oh, this room was kind of crazy.
Okay, okay.
Also, I should let my leech finish them off.
I don't think I'm gonna go in there.
Leech, do your thing.
Okay, he's killing one of them right now.
Nice.
Good job, Leech.
You can get the other ones.
I'm gonna damage them a little bit.
There you go.
Go.
Yeah, that's a good boy.
Nice.
Again, again.
I trust you.
Get him.
Kill him.
Yeah, dude, the leech.
Dude, I hate these masks.
They're kind of tough to deal with.
Nice.
Oh, yo, yo, yo.
Hey, you want to go finish him off?
Can you even go over there?
Get him.
Okay, you can't.
Full health.
Dude, I need devil deals now.
With all these hearts?
Not yet.
So, I can break rocks with this.
Oh, and we have this one, too.
Two red hearts.
If we get a step room, I'm totally down to do some stepping.
All right, Leech, I need you to go crazy now.
Ah, not that crazy.
You can kill one of them.
Go.
Get it.
Full health.
Nice.
And what do we have here?
Depression.
It's a dark cloud.
Spawns a trail of damaging creep.
Enemies that touch the cloud have a chance to be struck by a damaging light beam.
Very nice.
I don't know why I'm destroying this.
If I find something awesome, I'm just gonna be sad, because I can't get it.
Wait, what happened?
I don't know why this blew up.
Okay.
You know what?
It's worth it.
I can heal up easy.
That's fine.
I could activate in here and destroy all these rocks, and the skulls maybe find something cool.
I don't know if it's worth it, though.
Hold on a minute.
I didn't pay attention to how much damage up it was, but I guess it was pretty good.
Yeah, you're my friend.
Kill them.
Okay, Leech, I need you to kill them.
I do too much damage.
Why is my Leech just sort of standing there?
Ah, I think it was petrified.
It's healing me.
Full health.
Ah, never mind.
Go kill him.
Come on, Leech.
Yeah, beautiful.
Bad guess.
Question mark.
Okay, that was bad.
Ex-lax, ranged down.
No, thanks.
I'm good.
Move on.
Yeah, we're killing... we're going for Satan this time.
It's a good run.
We can kick his ass.
No doubt.
Oh, this guy's a champion!
Not bad.
What happened?
What just happened?
Was it depression?
Or was it... what just happened?
Purple Heart, no.
Huh.
I didn't lose a black card.
I don't know why that just happened.
Louse.
Small chance of spawning a blue spider anytime Isaac is in a room with enemies.
That doesn't sound too good.
What's this?
Child Leech?
Am I just falling more closely behind?
I wonder how that affects Leech.
Maybe that's a good thing?
No, I'll keep this actually.
I like having champions.
Let's go in here.
Nice.
This guy we can give so much HP to.
Oh my god!
Insanity.
Just like that.
Nice.
Wow.
Uh, move on.
Maybe let this guy finish them off a bit.
Oh, come on Leech.
Maybe the Leech is following me too closely now to actually do anything useful.
Did he kill him?
Get him!
Get him.
Nice.
Good job, good job.
Get him.
Good job.
Panic button.
Ah, we don't need that.
Lazy worm.
More damage, less shot speed.
Oh, I don't think that's good.
I need shot speed.
We can go step, ladies and gentlemen.
And we have some hearts.
And there's a machine we can use to get hearts.
We don't have that much money.
Let's keep exploring the rest of the place first.
Yeah, I have good damage now.
Oh, my Leech is killing everything.
See, now we're full health.
I wanted to leave and come back, but we have to kill the rest, unfortunately.
Because enemies are basically blood bags for me right now.
Okay, let me grab this.
Let's go up here.
Finally, a place I can use my keys.
What the hell?
Very nice.
I haven't seen this sort of thing before.
There's also a battery in there in case we need it.
Sick.
Oh, make it blow up the wall.
Okay.
Actually, I think there's a secret here.
No, there's not.
Maybe here.
What's up, greed?
You're not even ultra.
Oh, shit.
I'm gonna let the homeboy finish you off then.
Get him.
Yeah.
And we're rich.
Oh, baby.
We can totally go to the machine now.
Yeah, open up here.
Hmm.
Oh, we could also go... Wait a minute, let me think.
If I go to the boss now... So, I have 9% devil chance now.
If I step... You know what?
Let's try that.
I need to check this now.
Also, I think there's another secret on the left.
Right here.
But let me check from this side.
There.
Ah, okay.
It was a good bet though.
Okay, we have so much HP we can work with here.
Even more.
Okay, we're still at 9% devil though.
You feel blessed?
Okay, when this guy spawns, I'm gonna use my my active.
Is that toenail?
Uh, that's horrible.
I'm actually gonna come back.
I need more health.
Definitely.
I could also go in there.
No.
I've done that already.
We go... Where am I?
Oh, there.
We go this way.
To the right.
Thank you.
Now we're gonna gamble.
Come on, lots of hearts.
Lots of hearts.
I have minus one luck if it matters.
I don't want to step too much either.
If I don't get a good amount of hearts here, I may just not step.
Because I can see myself just losing.
Nice, we got it out of there.
Didn't destroy the machine.
Oh, this is not looking good.
Oh, man.
Wow, that was totally not worth.
Let's blow it up.
Damn, son.
Let's step two more times.
Maybe we get like... I was about to say we get a bunch of coins, but now we destroyed the machine, so fuck.
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh, yeah.
Damage is good.
Oh, shit.
That was bad.
And there it is.
A key piece.
This is the one that gives me some chance to, yeah, convert red hearts into eternal hearts.
So, wait a minute.
Let me see here.
So, according to this, I had angel spawn on nine and then another one on eleven, which means we're gonna go down to three hearts.
Wait, there's a shop.
Oh, why didn't I explore the shop?
I forgot about the existence of the shop.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's go get battery at least and activate our active again.
Give us a chance here.
Ah, frick.
There's another battery up here, though.
It was the good one.
Nice.
I'm gonna blow up some stuff here.
Look for more secrets.
So, we found one.
Ah, but this map is massive.
It could be anywhere.
I do wonder if there's like a specific rule set with that.
I mean, of course it is, because it's a game, right?
It's been coded.
But, you know what I mean.
Okay, let's go.
No, not that.
You know what we could do?
We could put it down beforehand.
Dropping the... during combat, dropping the trinket will cost mom to... Let's try this.
We're gonna do...
Oh, sick!
Shop time!
We're back, baby!
Okay, I'm leaving.
Let's go to the shop.
That's 30 coins right there.
Wow!
Uh, where am I going?
Let's just have the map open.
Look up here.
I have a key as well, in case we need to.
Here we are.
Pills.
Battery.
I don't like this very much.
Maybe the pill.
I can like the pill.
Oh!
Ah!
No!
Telepills!
Okay, that's fine.
I know where I am.
Yeah, I think we're done stepping.
We're done.
Let's go to the boss.
Uh, let's go.
Oh, wait, it's mom!
We need to play perfect.
I really fucked this up, guys.
I fucked it up.
Yes, mom.
Okay, we're doing good damage.
Nice.
Okay, no problem.
No problem, baby.
Easy.
Polaroid.
Taking damage with half or less red horse will trigger an invincibility.
Allows access to higher stages.
That's something I don't understand.
Because I have had access to the higher stages without this.
Unless it's talking about a different higher stage.
I'm thinking about the cathedral.
The church area.
Um, let's go.
Okay, now the mission is to heal up and find some black or blue hearts.
That seems good.
Let me also look for potential tinted rocks.
It looks like this one has a little X on it, but so does this one.
And there's no way there's two in one room, right?
So I'm gonna deem that not a tinted rock.
So far, so good.
I mean, it was bound to happen.
Let me scan this room.
Any X's in Texas?
I can't see shit because of my UI.
Let me actually just bomb this here.
Join my cause.
Kill him.
Yeah, good job, buddy.
Let me have a look here.
Nothing looks out of the ordinary.
What the hell are you?
Okay, you're gonna do that, huh?
I wonder if any of these enemies can ever charge downwards.
I don't think so.
It's always horizontal.
Kill him.
Yeah.
Do I get double healing from those guys?
No, I don't.
I don't.
Dude, this guy's just not dying.
Get him.
Come on, buddy.
Come on, leech.
Do your thing.
Wait, how did I just take damage?
Oh, I think I stepped on some creep there.
Okay, for some reason, leech is not cooperative right now.
That's okay.
Nothing suspicious in here.
Maybe this one, actually.
That one looks a little bit, but then we also have this one, which is the same.
It's the same as the one down there.
Okay.
Oh, I can't believe I did that again.
Dude, it's so hard to see.
It's like the same freaking color.
Anything in here?
Exes in Texas?
Nope, nothing.
Oh god, this guy's scary.
Thank you, little buddy.
Oh my god.
Oh, wow.
That was scary.
Oh, I can't even get that.
Too bad.
Yeah, we are not doing a good job of doing what I wanted to do, which is find healing.
South.
Oh my god, what is this?
Okay, little buddy, you better go out there and kill everyone.
Yes, keep healing me.
Keep healing me.
Oh, that's so nice.
Keep going, keep going.
Yeah, here we go.
This guy has a lot of HP, huh?
Good job.
And then we're gonna get extras from these.
We're triple dipping.
I shouldn't have.
That was a mistake.
It's okay.
Okay, any suspicious rocks?
No, not that I can see.
No.
Okay, buddy, you need to go.
Kill him.
Why are you stuck?
Okay.
Dude, I'm totally getting healed up here.
Get him.
Dude, what?
Okay.
Oh, the healing though.
Kill them all.
You gotta be shitting me.
I mean, the leech is so good.
Definitely saving my ass right now.
Yep, free healing.
I'm actually gonna go in here.
Don't even care.
Ansis.
Oh, nice.
Okay, let me actually look at the map.
So the secret rooms are located.
Let me actually think.
Where did I start?
Where did I come in?
I think I came in on the right side.
Below the the treasure room or the chest room.
So I wonder if it's like a minimum distance from start or something like that.
You know what I mean?
That's like a condition I can imagine.
Or how close they are together.
You know what?
I'm gonna take a picture of that.
Oh wait, it didn't work.
Wait, hold on.
Why can't I print screen on that?
Okay, there we go.
Print screen.
I'm gonna go in here.
Just zoom out a bit.
Oh, that's very small.
That's one.
Secret area locations right there, baby.
We're gonna be real scientific about this.
Treasure room or...
Wait, did we have a treasure room yet?
Ah, there's no treasure room here.
But at least I got out of that room without taking damage.
That's nice.
All right, Leech, go for it.
Oh, we're full health.
Okay.
It's going pretty well.
This is a nice run to start off with.
I feel so good inside my tummy right now.
That was also perfectly placed.
He wants keys.
I'm not gonna give it to him.
I gained devil chance from...
Okay, we're gonna note that down.
Let's see here.
Observations.
Killing a key beggar gives devil chance.
Yep.
At least sometimes.
I'm gonna get to the bottom of this.
Okay.
I love answers.
Stephen lives.
No, he doesn't.
I killed him.
Get a baby pet.
It will cheer you up.
It is dangerous to go alone.
Your princess is in another castle.
You know what?
I should come back to this later.
Because if I find a step room... Wait, I'm not gonna find a step room.
I can see all the rooms.
I never mind them.
I was gonna say we can go step and then grab the blue hearts after, right?
Have you seen the exit?
No.
Rebirth got cancelled.
Wake up.
Lies.
Jira.
How about the, uh, what's it called?
Lucky.
No, no, no.
I didn't take a picture of that.
You are dark inside.
What do you want to do today?
Uh, make tacos, actually.
Dude, I'm making tacos today.
I just decided that on the spot.
Okay, that's enough for now.
Chicken tacos.
Ow.
What's that?
Hemetemesis.
Hemetemesis is bad.
Hemetemesis never against this.
Gives one HP, man.
What the... I thought for sure it was gonna just heal me.
Never again.
We're gonna do that in the middle of combat.
Fuck me.
Imagine I threw everything on the floor.
Just now it... Oh, this is actually worth.
Nice.
Give me my heart.
Uh, there are a couple rooms I missed, but you know what?
That's fine.
I'll move on.
Uh, sponsor puddle of slippery creep.
Also, we have Jera.
Uh, hmm.
Oh, dude.
I should, uh... Wait, did I get...
Huh.
I should have used Jera on the blue hearts.
But that's okay.
We can maybe go back, get some more blue hearts.
Blast those cysts.
Let's do this.
Oh, wait.
This guy's on my side.
Hey, uh, you want to finish him off?
Go!
Get him!
Finish him!
Oh, wait.
We're not done yet.
Okay.
Finish him!
Come on, leech!
Go for it!
Why are you so useless?
Dude, really?
There we go.
Kill him.
A snack.
We love that because devil deals are gonna be...
Why are there so many deals?
I'm not looking at the deals.
I'm just dealing with these first.
Okay, let's see.
Gimpi, uh, chance to drop a soul heart when taking damage.
Chance to drop a half... Oh, that's really good.
But my luck is shit.
The dry baby.
Wait a minute.
Is this also conjoined?
No.
What is this?
Uh, death's list.
Okay, I know that one.
Take one heart of self-damage to gain a tears up and deal 40 damage.
Subsequent uses cost only... Oh, man.
That's a good...
Uh, that's actually pretty good.
But it's not that good.
I want Gimpi.
And then I want dry baby.
Yep.
And then I want death's list.
No, because my little leech is gonna fuck it up for me.
This is an active.
I like my current active.
We're good.
Solid.
I'm actually gonna go back to the other rooms.
Watch me find the most amazing thing in those rooms now.
Uh, not this way.
This way.
Well, there we go.
Look at that.
That's money right there.
Uh, oh, I don't actually want that.
I was hoping for some real money.
Not play money.
Uh, Steven?
Or leech?
Do you mind going?
Take care of him?
Okay, you can take care of the tomato first, but then you're gonna go on the guy, okay?
Come on.
Good job.
Wait, where'd he go?
What just happened?
Why did he disappear?
That was weird, wasn't it?
Okay, now we leave.
And there's no step room or anything like that, so we are actually just cleared for leaving.
Did I see an X here?
No.
X, X, X, X, X, checking all the rocks.
They are so incredibly hard to spot.
I don't need keys.
I'm going.
Now comes, it lifts.
Shouldn't be a problem.
I did actually forget.
I wanted to go back to the machine and get lucky with blue hearts and then Jira, but maybe it's okay.
I'm not gonna pick anything up in here on purpose.
Oh, we're gonna duplicate that.
I mean, come on.
That was pretty cool, huh?
29 coins ready to be gambled when we need to.
Wait, why are you... Oh, you're scared.
What is that?
I need it.
I want it.
No.
Why so cruel?
Actually, let's do this.
Hey, hey.
Wait, was that actually a rock?
A tinted rock?
Ambilical cord.
When entering a room with half a red heart, I'll scan a little Steven.
So, Steven does live.
They weren't lying.
30% chance of taking damage.
Spawn a Gemini.
But it scales with luck and my luck is shit.
So, I'm good.
I haven't seen any real, like, champion enemies.
Obviously, I was expecting a lot more.
Okay, that was my familiar that just did that.
Chance of him taking damage, you know, deals room-wide damage.
Or blocking shots for me.
Ah, no problem.
You can actually see where they're going when they're feared.
The debuff follows them on the ground.
Nice.
Okay, so it's closed here.
What is our current situation?
We have 9% demon this time.
Minus one luck again.
Maybe it is tied to luck.
Could be.
And notice, it's the skull again.
Skull door.
Maybe it's like... Maybe it's something related to my current utility.
So, if I have, like, less than x amount of coins, bombs, or keys, the game will, like, okay, you know, here's a bone.
We're gonna throw you a bone and give you the opportunity to earn some of that back, because you don't have anything.
I don't think that's the case, but could be.
Evil poop.
Don't mind that at all.
Filigree feather.
Wait, we unlocked that last time!
Defeated angels will drop angel room items instead of key pieces.
Whoa!
If a key piece was previously collected, angels will spawn the other key piece before producing angel items.
Oh!
You know what?
Let's run with that.
I like it.
He's taking a full heart now, by the way, this guy.
That's all I'm giving him.
Unless I, you know, get full health again, then I'll come back.
Give me that, and this one, and that one.
Nice.
No!
The light beam sabotaged my healing!
No way!
Oh, not this!
I can't do this.
Unless I can.
Ah, wait.
Ah!
Fine.
Kiss!
Get him!
I mean, okay.
I think he needs a little bit of help.
I'm gonna shoot one shot.
Oh, no!
He got him!
His DPS is just...
a little too low.
Yeah, there we go.
He needed a little nudge there at the end.
Nice!
Oh my god, I love that baby!
Beautiful.
Really should have let my little guy finish him off, but automatically restores the final charge.
Nah, not needed.
Also, I have to remember that the current item I have, the active, can remove objects in a room.
If I really need to.
Okay, little buddy, go nuts in here!
Kill everyone!
I believe in you!
Heal me up!
He found a target!
Sweet.
Ah, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We can't be losing HP like that.
That makes this all not worth it.
Now, we can't jump over holes.
Okay, I didn't get any HP there for some reason.
Just blow this up.
Boss is there.
Oh, no.
Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi.
Go for it, buddy!
Kill them all!
Yeah, good job!
Keep it up!
Yes, you're so good!
Okay, do you mind finishing him off?
Oh, okay, never mind.
Missed the room over here.
This run has been so good.
Although, I would love to get a couple more black hearts.
Oh, you know what I could do?
I just realized I should have been using my active more often just to create more black hearts.
Because if I don't take damage, I can essentially stack them.
Shit, I didn't think about that.
But, of course, that makes so much sense.
Secret room, baby!
Doubles keys, I mean.
60 keys.
Oh, wait, re-roll?
But there's nothing to re-roll unless you're talking about the little baggy?
Am I wasting my money?
Oh, lock-up, nice!
That's something.
Yeah, weird.
Okay, I think we're gonna kill the boss.
But wait a minute, if I do this, I can't go back.
I think.
No, we're good.
Let's do this.
First the eyes.
That was so good.
Yeah, I love it.
Okay, we got brainiacs up here.
Uh-oh, what is this?
This is a new attack.
Wait, this is all new.
Okay, this is fine, this is fine.
My damage is not that good.
Yeah, no problem.
I forgot we did this!
Yeah!
I totally forgot!
That's what we were doing here.
Completely forgot.
That's amazing.
Okay, um, what is... I need to take this.
Sacrificial dagger, my fate protects me.
Orbital knife familiar that deals heavy contact damage.
Okay, so that is the same one that uh, insert the other character has that I've been playing.
Monster manual, I don't think I want that.
I'm good without it.
Now, uh, let me see.
I think I'm gonna...
I'm going down.
That's right.
Oh, you can even see the upside down cross in the little preview in the top right.
That's funny.
Didn't notice that before.
Oh my god.
I got backed into a corner!
Dude, where's... there you are.
Okay, let's calm down.
No reason to rush anything now.
Just take it easy.
We're gonna calm and collectively let these guys kill each other and heal up.
That's good, that's good.
Yes, good job, little buddy.
Wonderful.
Telepills, uh, why not?
It's not teleporting.
That was so smart.
I did it on purpose there to potentially open a secret.
What?
Okay, sure.
Nothing exciting, though.
Too bad.
Super greed.
Yeah, but you're not ultra greed, are you?
You ain't nothing.
We have a way down here.
Oh, he's not enemies.
Oh, they shoot lasers?
No way!
Okay, little guy, can you go finish them off for me?
Oh no, you gotta be kidding me.
I'm not doing well.
That's okay,
that's okay.
Okay, what if you don't have a bomb here?
Are you soft block in that case?
Like, obviously I can just get into him, but I'm just wondering right now, what's let's say I didn't have a bomb or I didn't have the opportunity to destroy all these rocks, like what would I do then?
You know?
I feel like that's a funny situation there.
Maybe the game would recognize that I couldn't access and then just open the door.
It could be a thing, I guess.
Yeah, it would make sense to coat that in, right?
Okay buddy, you need to heal me.
Nice, keep healing me.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Come on, come on, come on, get him, get him.
No!
Oh, Jesus!
Man, I'm not good at shield.
Those guys are scary.
Heal me?
Maybe it's too risky to let this guy heal me.
Yeah, it's too risky man, just kill him.
But look at this, we may have an opportunity here.
I'm gonna do it here in case there's a secret.
No!
Finish him off!
Yeah, yeah, okay!
Yeah, okay, well.
Although,
I guess I negated the damage by using my active.
Nice, love when that triggers.
Good, it's not that bad.
We're slowly healing up here.
Oh, let's not forget the bomb strategy against Satan.
That was a mega discovery last time.
I'm gonna save my bombs.
Oh, I thought you puked.
Sweet.
I don't know what I need to do here before the boss.
I think I'm just good, honestly.
Perhaps grab this.
Okay, finish him off.
Wait, it's not always that I get healed from it.
It's only sometimes, it seems.
Confirm that?
No, it does say definitively.
Maybe it just didn't look properly.
Or maybe he died to my creep.
That could be a thing.
Maybe he stepped on my creep, you know.
Though these guys are actually evil.
Dice room!
Oh, hell nah.
No.
No, thanks.
That is a bad idea.
You want to go finish him off?
Here, this one's yours.
You got him, you got him, come on.
Get him, get him.
No, sabotage by the light beam.
Shit.
Fuck, I should have done that in the boss room.
Whoops.
I fucked it up.
We have the devil though, we can use that in here.
I can't believe I just did that.
Oh wait, this is not even a mega dude.
Ah, it's gonna be no problem.
I got you mixed up.
Let me prepare a bomb for you.
Oh wait, it's not yet.
We gotta wait until the the shoes come in.
Wait for the shoes.
Oh my god.
Dude, I'm totally throwing this.
Yeah, dude!
Yeah!
That was so close.
So close.
Not bad.
Man,
good first run, huh?
And unlock the new character.
Okay.
Broken Ankh has appeared.
Nice.
Okay, uh, let's do... we obviously gotta go for the new character.
Bethany, Book of Virtues.
All right, why not?
First, let's check it.
Wait, I have some kind of... why can't I see my active?
Hello.
Three hearts though is pretty good.
Spawns a little flame.
Okay, uh, what am I doing in here?
I guess I'll just do this.
No problem.
We have 2.7 damage.
I would say that's pretty average.
Nothing special there.
Looks like I have two charges on this thing.
I need to pay attention to what this actually does, this little familiar.
It's not automatically attacking.
Maybe contact damage.
Okay.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a minute.
I have a blue heart, uh, tool on the left.
What the hell is that?
Huh?
What's that all about?
Well, that's new.
Let's figure out what that means.
I'm guessing we need to collect blue hearts, and then something awesome happens.
Back up.
Give me a treasure room, baby.
Oh, let me see these.
Uh, so, okay, attack, bomb, item, okay.
But you can, you can see the, um, the drawings are actually reflecting my character, right?
So I thought maybe they're gonna explain that new thing to me.
Oh, open, please.
Ah, damn.
I was hoping for a secret room there.
Oh, bro!
Did we just lose battery?
Because I took damage, or...
Wait.
I didn't take any damage.
A lot of the martyr damage up, okay.
Okay, let's straight up just damage up.
Uh, okay, so what do I do now?
No bombs.
I still have my little familiar with me.
I don't know, I'm not sure what it's doing.
Okay, the haunt.
I'm gonna haunt this guy's dreams.
Okay, so my flight has appeared.
I'm gonna make another one.
What the?
Bro!
Predictive!
The movement of those guys is something else.
Yeah, good.
Dude, I'm hitting with every shot.
Never mind.
Almost every shot.
Nice.
All in all, not too bad.
Dinner.
Ah, amazing.
I have been loving everything so far about this run.
So good.
Let's go.
I love that Isaac was so happy about getting the wig, you know.
Isaac seems like a cool dude to hang out with.
100% angel!
Are we like Jesus or something?
We have the Jesus cap on and everything.
Look at it.
I think this is the the whole deal with this character.
We are actually so religious that maybe the devil doesn't even want to bother with us.
We're going straight to angels.
Oh, shit.
That's a lot.
You guys gonna throw a bomb?
Yeah.
Chill.
Ah, crap.
I saw a good amount of coins here.
Oh, dude.
Blowing this up here is ideal.
I got a tinted rock and a coin for that.
Bombs are needed.
No more keys.
Need bombs.
Two of spades.
What did that do?
Doubles the keys.
I really want to find blue hearts and see what's going on with that stat on the left.
Oh, sick.
Early luck.
Surely come in handy.
Best of both.
Sponsor fly familiar.
Yeah, okay.
That's fine.
Still 100% angel, by the way.
Let's see if it changes when we take damage.
I'm not gonna take damage on purpose, but we gotta see what's going on.
Come here.
Nice.
I'm gonna spawn a little dude here.
We got erratic people.
Uh, oh, I shouldn't have done that.
Oh, it's okay.
Um, pills.
Oh, I would love the blue map.
That would be so nice to have.
Uh, yeah.
Try to corner me.
Did you see that?
Flanking me.
Pincer maneuver.
Too many enemies.
Blew.
Oh, we lost angel.
Must have been that.
Fuck.
Uh, Ouroboros worm.
This one is...
You know, it's cool.
Yeah, it's fine.
We can always take it off, right?
I fuck with it.
I just gotta get used to the shooting patterns here a little bit.
Uh, there we go.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just keep spawning these guys, because I think it may be good.
Ha!
Hit him!
Okay, you know what?
No, thanks.
I'm good, son.
Keep it.
The damage up is nice, but it's not worth it.
Not at all.
Ah, man, where's my bombs?
You gotta be... Wait, was there a bomb in the shop?
I didn't actually pay attention.
Let's go double check.
I think there may have been a bomb in the shop.
There was a bunch of stuff in the shop.
Oh, baby!
Let's go.
Very nice.
There's also a heart in there that I can potentially pick up after defeating the boss.
Are you ready for the best bomb of all time?
Not bad.
Okay, yeah, we got an upgrade in the blue heart department there.
So, I don't know what that means, though.
Let's try to pay attention.
We have two blue hearts now, and eight coins.
Maybe I buy something else.
Let me see what that is.
Ah, I'll leave it.
Time for the boss.
Also, I'm gonna try and spawn more than one of these guys that I have with my active.
Maybe they merge into, like, a big one at some point, if I do it enough.
No, it got destroyed.
So, he ran into it and it got, like, like a mini explosion.
Fizzled out.
Oh, my!
He caught me off the corner!
Oh, wait, I have a fly now.
Oh, this fly did a lot of damage to him.
Uh... Angel!
Oh, nice.
Chance of burning...
I guess that's good, right?
Especially for this character, where everything is relying on that somehow.
Oh, what am I doing?
I should have done that.
Dude, I should have blown up the angel.
Why didn't I do that?
Whoops.
Oh, well.
Um, okay.
Eight coins.
There's nothing else I want to do on this floor.
We move on.
Here's a flower.
Whoops.
Peepee.
I will not take any damage on this floor.
Nice.
Spawns a beggar.
No, thanks.
Not right now.
Oh, man.
Don't tease me like this.
Okay.
That was a bit scary.
Okay, you know what?
It's fine.
It's okay.
I didn't mean what I said anyway.
I was joking.
Like, these rooms are just killer.
Sesame, open up.
Fuck.
I may not be addicted to pills.
Like, I had that insane pill run yesterday.
Like, that was incredible.
Sweet.
I'm actually gonna go in.
Oh, my god.
Get the tomato out of here.
I feel like I'm killing more tomatoes than boss right now.
Okay, here's... oh, my god.
It's going horribly.
Yeah, man.
The orbital fly I have is doing a lot of damage.
Please!
Oh, Jesus.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, uh, yeah, sure, whatever.
Wait, we're still at two blue hearts.
Why?
Shouldn't that be three now?
Oh, man, I really want to get in here.
I kind of want to step.
I'm gonna... uh, no, no, no, not yet, not yet.
Find some HP.
Oh, shit.
That's scary.
Man, just no bombs, huh?
They do not exist in this world.
Ah, here we go, though.
Oh, and the matchstick is so huge.
We're gonna find more bombs this way.
We're stuck in the wrong configuration.
Ha!
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
I noticed that we charged up the book with the heart.
But it's weird that we get two blue hearts, and then after that we start charging up the book.
I don't know what that's about.
What?
Why two?
That's so weird.
Huh.
It's probably a good reason for that.
He can break most obstacles by walking over them.
Hmm, not bad.
I'm gonna be breaking everything.
Scary.
I have an unusual talent for missing completely at point blank range.
More bombs, huge.
Oh, yeah, I can eat everything.
Man,
I would love that coupon.
So, wait, blue hearts are kind of shit.
I don't care about charging the book with blue hearts.
That sounds absolutely terrible.
Like, why would I take this one?
I can take the battery.
Maybe we can save up for the coupon.
Ah, should I or should I not?
Nah, we're not gonna go in there.
Wait, we're at one blue heart now.
Huh?
Oh, maybe I...
maybe I consumed it by using the book.
Fuck.
Is that what's happening?
So, I I consume battery, but I also consume the blue heart.
Really weird.
I need four more coins.
Can it be done?
Maybe if I blow this guy up.
Fuck, yeah, it can be done.
Copon!
We're gonna make everything free.
But wait, am I gonna replace my book then?
What?
I now have a coupon in between the pages of my book.
Uh, what the fuck is going on here?
Times... wait, hold on, uh, makes what item in the shop are devil room free?
So, uh, x1 middle wisp?
Two hp, three damn triple shot?
Wisps are destroyed when anything is purchased.
Huh?
Is that a triple shot?
Oh, no, wait.
Oh, my little guy is shooting!
I have a green one now!
Oh, wait!
Huh,
three three blue hearts and we gain...
I see.
All right, this is... uh, I'm not sure I fully understand everything yet.
We're gonna have to experiment with that.
Yeah.
Interesting, though, that's... it sort of combines with the coupon.
That's weird.
Oh!
Oh, yeah, I can eat things!
Sick.
I don't want to speed down.
That's horrible.
We're at five blue hearts now.
Vrp.
Oh, no.
I don't like that.
Oh!
What?
I don't know what just happened.
I got pooped on or something.
Ooh, ah, speed.
Dude, I made a bridge by eating!
Huh.
Oh!
I don't like this.
What the hell is up with that?
Okay, moving on.
I need to find a shop now and use my coupon and go crazy.
How are you gonna dodge that?
Brother!
It's over.
We're done.
Yeah, we're done.
Jesus fucking christ, bro.
Those mushrooms can suck me.
That was horrible.
Okay, let's try something else.
Once and for all, we're gonna be done with this challenge now.
I'm gonna channel everything I've got into this one now.
Everything.
Immediately gonna do that, even though I should have done it in here.
I'm gonna blow this up to get in there.
We're not gonna pick it up.
Right now, we're just Judas, but better.
Okay, blow that up.
Huge.
We're not gonna fuck this one up.
We are going to win.
The damage is good.
It's really good, actually.
Eight damage.
This early on.
You can't really beat that.
This is a weird room.
Yeah, go for it.
Monstro.
This is one of the harder ones, in my opinion.
Just when he jumps, it's very not nice.
Okay, but my damage is good.
Oh, nice, nice, nice.
I shall take that.
Why not?
We're gonna not cut ourselves yet.
Happens later.
Because we're playing smart now.
No mistakes.
Burp, burp, burp, burp, burp.
Come here.
I can't get in there.
That is such a tease.
Slice those veins.
We're gonna get in there deep.
Okay.
No suspicious rocks.
Not bad.
I will maybe not blow that guy up, because I don't have any money.
Double check if there's a door.
There's no door.
I... no.
I'm gonna save my blue hearts.
Okay.
Wait, what was this?
All right.
Hold on, I gotta take off my watch.
It's annoying me.
I gotta get a new, like, band for that watch.
It's horrible.
Okay, this way.
Not this way.
Yeah, having a question mark for a map is not...
Bro, I'm so lost.
I have no idea where to go.
This way?
Not that way.
I mean, it's not here.
I just came from here.
Unless it is here.
Oh, it is here.
Okay.
It was indeed there.
That was a decent first floor.
In fact, very decent.
We're going full speed here.
Well, not full speed, but 80% speed.
At least we have a minimap.
No.
Not right now.
Line him up!
Uh, nine coins is not that bad.
Definitely buying that.
We could take a pill.
No, let's save it.
Saving the pill.
One of these are gonna shoot green stuff at me?
No, okay, maybe not.
Fuck you!
Ruined my streak.
Uh, don't take that.
Speed is pretty good.
Stop with your erratic walking.
Growth hormones!
Nice.
Uh, yeah.
Definitely taking a deal.
In fact, we should go down to zero red hearts.
No, one red heart.
Let's see what we got here.
Ghost baby.
And, uh, ooh.
Huh.
Now that could be good, actually.
I'm taking this.
I'm gonna take that.
Yeah, now we're at one.
And then if we get more, we're gonna, you know, exchange for three blue.
This is the plan.
Uh, let me see.
Yeah.
We're not gonna go below one just because I'm scared.
Decent second floor as well.
I think this is going pretty good.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god.
I can't stop thinking about the tacos I'm gonna make.
Uh, I don't want to get in there.
We need flying.
Or something.
Now, this may not be a big surprise, but getting better at this game is actually making the game even more fun.
Wow, what a surprise.
No, but really, like, especially so in this game.
You can really feel the difference, you know?
Come here.
Man, when he doesn't have a body, he's so unpredictable.
Down and right.
What's up, wrath?
Oh yeah, you want to blow yourself up?
Be my guest.
Make another bomb, nerd.
Dumbass.
Aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, what was that?
What was that even?
Troll bombs.
You know what?
Let's use that against the boss.
I have a good feeling.
Oh, I could donate a little bit here.
Yeah, sick.
Fight room, I'll take it.
Dobby's tail, why not?
What does that do, actually?
Oh, we're two out of three now, as well.
Increases chance of chests as room clear rewards, but also increases chance of no reward at all.
All right, all right, all right.
That one I'm still a little iffy about.
But two out of three?
I don't actually recall what three out of three does, but it's surely good, right?
That was evil!
Evilism.
Wowie.
Maybe I shouldn't open chests during combat.
Lesson learned, maybe.
More spiders.
Oh yeah, right, the door opened.
Okay, okay.
I don't want to open that door yet, unless we have 15 coins, and we can get 15 coins easily.
If I can go up here, I can grab hearts and donate more.
Yuck.
There's gonna be something good in there.
You'll see.
Not bad.
Oh, interesting.
Should we do that?
That sounds fun, doesn't it?
This could be amazing.
Or it could be terrible.
Oh, I'm an idiot!
I saw the red text!
And I was like, oh, that's the other one.
I can't believe I've done this.
At least we get to break rocks now.
That's something.
Oh, that's actually kind of fun.
I like that.
Can I break the machine?
Oh, whoops.
For some reason, I thought, oh yeah, I can't donate anything other than red hearts.
That's not how that works.
Half a heart wasted there.
Wait, what?
Okay, okay.
I understand how it works now.
I activate the pickaxe, and then I'm in pickaxe mode.
Oh, I was like, oh shit, I can't shoot anymore, but I can.
Scary.
Hey, hey!
Not bad.
Can I make a bridge here?
Oh, I don't think so.
Too bad.
Nothing.
Shit.
Oh, stay... I was at range!
Okay, I guess you can't be out of range then with this.
I feel like that never happens to me with the mushrooms.
Like, it's never happened before today.
I'm not sure why that's a thing all of a sudden.
Pick that up.
Okay, go back and pick up the other one then.
I want this, and then I guess I'll take that one.
And yeah, that's it.
I'm good.
Then again, do I want this even?
At this point, when I'm so low on HP, I don't think so.
I'm gonna take this instead.
Yeah.
Oh, hey, look at this!
Hey, hey!
Nice!
Ah, there we go.
Give me that back.
We can get in here.
Give me blue hearts.
Blue hearts, please.
Okay, wish me luck.
The holo, we have to play perfect here.
And this is gonna be a tough one, because these guys are fast!
Huge.
Yeah, it plays.
Oh, that's huge.
I like that.
I like that a lot.
We can go back as well.
Door stop.
Hey.
Oh, no.
He's gonna do a laser?
Yeah, stay in the fire!
Dumbass.
Man, how do I know which direction?
What the hell?
It's just guessing.
He always drops the coal every time.
It's confirmed now.
I mean, it's pretty good.
It's okay.
Find item.
I don't... not mind it.
Wait, does that make sense?
What I just said?
Maybe.
Okay.
We can go heal up again.
And then we move on.
I don't want to stay at 1 HP.
Even though it gives me damage, it's just too risky.
This is not looking good, man!
We need more healing.
Yeah.
This room is really difficult.
I hate this.
I can never get to that chest.
I've never been able to get to that chest.
We need flying for that.
Decent.
Not for me.
Arcade.
I have 20 coins.
That's an empty arcade.
There's no games.
Unlimited bacon, but no games.
Oh god.
Okay.
We're really gonna look now.
Hold on.
Oh, money!
Sick.
Let's check the items.
10 items.
Doorstop, the tower.
Stats, health, and...
Okay.
It's insane.
I have no idea what that does.
Gimme.
Okay, humbling bundle.
Oh, I should definitely...
Whoa, wait!
I should have used the active to get three blue hearts.
Wait, hold on.
Actually, there's something good here.
What was it?
Increases chance of chests?
Not that one.
No.
Okay, never mind.
But I could take this.
I've got the money for it.
Yeah, that's fine.
Good.
Clean.
Ooh.
Oh, please, blue hearts.
I'll take it.
Not bad.
That's a big fly.
I've never seen that.
So many heart drops as well.
We could potentially go step.
Actually, we could step.
But that's gonna... Oh, it's gonna ruin my blue hearts.
So, unless I lose them.
Let's It's tough.
This is gonna be a tough one here.
Actually, I do pretty good damage.
Here's a bomb for you.
Enjoy.
Nice.
Solid.
Yep, more damage is fantastic.
I'm interested in making a deal.
This is totally worth.
We got a black card as well.
Yeah, speed down.
We don't like that.
Fantastic deal.
Then again, it does give me damage.
Maybe, actually, you know what, it is worth.
Speed.
That's totally worth.
I'm not done exploring.
Jar of Flies.
Add some blue flies with the jar for each enemy kill.
Uh, that could actually be okay.
But I do like the mining pig.
The mining pig is fun.
I just gotta be careful with the mushrooms.
In fact, maybe the mushrooms only do that thing when... Oh, you know what?
I can do this.
Maybe the mushrooms only spawn the damage when you use the pickaxe, because I've never seen that happen with bombs.
I don't think so.
I'm just gonna go back and forth a little bit here.
Hey!
Nice!
We're gonna be ready for the next shop now.
Ooh, sick.
Feels kind of wasteful to take two hearts there, but you know.
What are you gonna do?
29 coins.
And we're not even done.
Actually, we are done.
This is the last heart.
I will pick this up.
No, we're not done.
Give me that.
One more time.
And treasure rooms.
But wait a minute.
Are there even treasure rooms in the challenge?
I don't think there is.
In fact, I don't even remember seeing one.
Yeah, fuck it.
We move on.
Yep.
Wrap this.
And let's go.
Now, what is the plan?
Play well.
Rainbow!
Wow.
I guess it's nice to look at.
Oh, you bastard.
Ruining my black heart here.
That's a black lord.
Black heart.
Since you ruined my black heart, I will murder your entire civilization of flies.
Everyone dies.
What is this?
Oh, wait.
No, don't just suck.
I can't do it.
Maybe later.
That was actually clean.
You know what?
Sick.
Just like that.
Okay, I'm too scared to destroy the bomb.
Yo, how much does it do to enemies?
Oh, wow.
Spot a chest.
Oh, oh, geez.
Jera.
Oh, if we find blue hearts, we have to remember this.
This is the thing that may change the run.
Gotta be on the lookout.
Now, what is what is this?
Nah, not good.
You're gonna look at me.
There we go.
Nice.
Come on, then.
What the?
It actually murdered both hands.
Wow.
I don't even know my own strength.
Oh, man, I nailed this room.
Clean.
Oh, that was close.
A little scary.
One spider holding up everything.
Nice.
Pure stats.
I take that.
And we are rich.
The jar.
That could actually be pretty good.
I'm gonna buy this.
The world!
Love that.
Do I want this?
Up to four hearts can be stored at once.
I mean, it's only good if we're gonna do stepping or something.
Yeah, even then.
I guess it's good for blood donation.
But nah, I'm not feeling it.
Let's go back to the secret room.
Very nice.
And the other one.
There is no other one.
Okay.
So, I guess it's randomized between one or two.
Let's go up here.
Oh, and we can see what the boss is.
Maybe I should actually just go for the... No, keep going.
This is good.
We're doing good.
Playing it safe.
Oh, god!
What am I doing in here?
There's nothing for me!
This area is just a death trap.
Yeah.
That was horrible.
Oi, yo, yo.
Sick.
Playing pretty well.
Okay, here we go.
The adversary.
A coin!
Oh, you bastard.
Are you gonna laser me again?
You are.
Did I dodge that?
You're gonna laser?
What's happening?
Okay.
Oh, man.
Bastard.
Oh, at least we got one of these.
Sick.
Yeah.
Not bad.
Is there anything I'm missing here before I go?
Let me think.
I say that and then I'm gonna remember in exactly three seconds.
Okay, nice.
Let's go here.
I think this is now mom.
Oh, my god.
Gravity strong.
Oh, massive!
That's huge.
This is gravity, though.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nice.
Okay, you want coins.
I have a lot of that.
You can have it.
Why am I bombing when I can just do that?
Give me a bunch of blue hearts so I can jar this.
This is the plan.
Sure.
Let me make some room for myself.
Is that it?
What?
What is that?
Firing for four seconds releases a small fart cloud that can be pushed with tears.
The cloud increases in size and okay.
All right.
Sure.
I'm not ready to boss yet, though.
I need to find some blue hearts here.
Ideally more than... Oh, shit.
Ideally more than one.
One is just... Oh, no, mom!
I totally missed that.
Careful.
Okay.
I could have jarred there, but that's not worth it.
We don't need money that much.
Damn!
Wow.
It's going horribly.
Oh, my god.
Wow.
There's fart clouds everywhere.
I don't like this room.
I don't like what's going on right here.
Yeah, fuck that.
It's just impossible.
Uh, I don't know what I want.
This is probably...
Oh, I thought there was a door down here.
Jackie, no, you cannot jump up at the table.
Oh, how
do I dodge this?
Okay, that works.
That works.
No, not these fucking bastards.
I can't tell you how much I hate these.
Get me out of here.
Kill them.
Push.
Okay.
One left.
We're going to end up losing this run again.
We're not going to be able to do this challenge.
Why do I always end up in this freaking situation with this character every time?
Okay, come on.
Uh, we need more HP.
Please, something amazing.
Oh, it doesn't look that good, though.
This looks like crap.
Consumes a red heart container.
I don't have any useless shops.
What is that?
That's bombs, right?
Yeah.
Uh, taking three... Yeah, whatever.
Hate having money and not being able to use it on anything useful.
Uh, not worth duplicating.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
I need everything you got.
We can also give this guy some stuff.
Let's try not to die to this guy, huh?
Uh,
oh.
Sketal?
Okay, that's fine.
I need to grab some hearts here.
Go back and grab the other heart.
Okay, uh, do we have any other hearts?
We have one heart up north, so we can do a little bit more.
Damn.
Nothing.
We got here and rights.
Oh, that's two hearts here.
Sick.
We could get something really good.
Uh, for the current room, yeah, that's pretty good, I guess.
Maybe I'll save that for something.
Uh, okay.
I don't think that's good for me.
Yeah, that's bad.
Now we grab the last heart we have.
Like, that arcade is going to save my run, hopefully.
It is the only hope we have, Obi-Wan.
We're my only hope.
Dark, uh, what's this?
Consumes red heart pick up some drops.
Yes!
That sounds good!
Now we gotta get something good from this guy.
I don't want that.
Ah, wait, are you gonna convert that to a black one as well, or how was it?
Ah, let's see here.
Only red hearts.
Okay, shit.
Better than nothing.
Well, time for the boss.
Here we go.
Oh, down there.
Dude, you were so fast!
Just keep jumping.
Jump, jump, everybody go.
I swear to god this challenge is going to be the end of me.
We're doing it again.
I can't fucking stand this challenge.
I don't know why I end up in this situation every time.
I think I've decided I hate the Whore of Babylon.
It may be the worst character in the game, just because of these experiences that I have here.
It is just so annoying.
And it's not like she has anything innately bad about her, but she's just horrible, just based on statistical track record.
That's lucky.
Wait, what's happening in here?
What is that?
Oh, I mean, keys are not going to be an issue.
That's some good shit right there.
Okay.
Oh, I mean, this start is really good.
But it's always going to go to shit later anyway.
This is like the experience every time, you know, it's really good at first and then...
Callous.
That's amazing.
Love that one.
Reduce the amount of damage I can take.
Hiding in the corner there.
You're going to charge me?
I mean, pretty good.
Not bad at all.
Do I want to go to the shop?
No, not really.
Not with two coins.
It's just going to bring me sadness.
Cellar.
100% demon mode.
But you know what?
Demons are actually bad on this character.
This is something I just realized.
We don't want demons.
Because we have no HP.
Infinite keys, though, is going to be very nice.
Oh, I had money!
Oh, man.
Six start.
Rarely gets better than this.
And this is closed.
Oh, nice.
One of my stuff just blocked that shot.
Saved me.
Okay.
Good to get it over with.
Now we know that that is a paralysis pill.
Well, sure.
Now that I'm rich, of course.
Hive mind.
Blueflies and spiders do double damage.
But, I mean, that's not even good because I don't have any blueflies or spiders.
I feel like this is a bad item.
Unless you have another item that is good with this in a synergistic way, you know?
This is obviously good.
Starter deck, maybe.
As it can hold two cards at once.
All future pill drops are replaced with cards.
I mean, that could be pretty fun.
Let's do that one instead.
And we get teleport to the secret room.
I like it.
Now we have enough to buy... what was that item in there?
Something that cost five that I wanted.
Oh, yeah.
The blue heart.
We can take that now.
Very nice.
Oi, yo, yo.
We have a tinted rock.
I mean, this start is freaking phenomenal.
This is the run.
It has to be the run.
If it's not the run, I will be so sad that I may actually, you know, skip tacos today just to punish myself.
This run is going to determine whether or not I'm going to star.
Sure.
If I win this run, I will sit happily tonight, eat tacos, and watch television shows with Jackie.
If I don't win this run, I'm going to cry myself to bed.
And no food.
And no games.
Or bacon.
A glass eye makes us lucky.
Okay, listen.
Wait, Satanic Bible?
Plus one black heart on use.
Okay.
Activating this before defeating the current floor's boss will replace the boss reward with a devil deal item that costs health to claim.
Oh, oh, okay.
This is a double-edged sword.
Oh, that is actually... I need to think about that.
Let me think about it while I dodge these spiders.
Satanic Bible.
What if the Satanic Bible will work against Satan?
Imagine it's like the inverse of the Bible, where it kills mom, this one kills Satan, right?
But the fact that it gives a black heart every time is actually massive.
I need it.
I'm going to regret it.
I just did a massive blunder, probably.
I'm going to starve tonight.
I'm going to starve.
Oh, man.
Okay.
So before we clear any rooms at all, we do this so we can gain maximum energy on this.
Oh, I can't even see my HP.
No!
Okay, just don't take any damage, dumbass.
Can't be that hard.
Okay, good.
The boss is here.
Uh, yeah.
Why not?
That is the fastest boss I've ever found.
Isn't that crazy?
Okay, you can keep doing that.
That's fine.
Oi, yoi, yoi.
He's going to spawn another one of these.
Yeah.
I'm scared.
That's for you.
Huge.
Actually massive.
I don't want that item.
I do want this item.
Oh, my God.
Am I going to go in here?
He's going to drop the lump of coal, this piece of shit.
No!
Bump.
Shit.
Die, die, die.
Okay, good.
Oh, no, he's not going to...
Okay.
Fires a brimstone laser attack and... Oh, why is it an active?
I can't take it.
I need this active.
This is what I need.
Holy rich.
Show me a shop now.
I can't reach.
That's crazy.
This is going to go like this.
Ultimate safety.
That almost hit me.
Can I get across somehow?
I don't think so.
Nah.
Too bad.
Please.
Something good.
Oh, let's use this.
What did we forget?
What is this?
Quicker chart.
Yeah.
Not bad at all.
Let me see this thing.
Automatically restores one charge bar actor after active item use.
Items with a one room recharge become an automatic timed recharge.
Wait, what does that mean?
Items.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
Fully charges Isaac's active item on pickup.
Got it.
That is very good.
I think I have a lot of black hearts right now.
And it feels incredible to say.
Especially because tacos are coming in.
Oh, you don't even think about it.
Have you ever seen a room like this?
What is that?
10% increased chance of finding a card as a room clear reward or add additional cards, chest, whatever.
This one is useless to me because there's no treasure rooms.
Flat penny.
No, this is the doorstop.
And what's that one?
And blue flies a spot.
Dude, I hate.
I don't like any of these.
Useless.
That room looks so cool, but it was just window dressing.
Oh, window dressing.
Now there's a chest here that I really want.
But I can't get it.
Boss has been defeated already.
That's such a nice relief.
It opened.
Why?
Okay, wait, notice this is not the skull room.
This is not the skull room.
So why did it open?
We have plus one luck.
Maybe.
It is consistent with everything else today, except that it's not the same type of room.
But I think they do share some similarities.
Oh, no.
Didn't I make a rule earlier not to open chests while fighting?
Why am I doing it then?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Thank you, bird.
Nice.
Oh, this is the run.
I will be fed tonight.
Oh, didn't even see you there.
Not that we need more keys.
Yeah, we're good to leave.
But I think there's a secret.
Not here.
Here.
Okay, I'll show myself out.
Um, you know.
No, no, no, it's an active.
Oh, my God.
Look at the HP.
I'm eating good tonight.
Literally.
That is insane.
Would love to get a bit more speed on my shots.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, no, thanks.
I'm not gonna go ahead and do that.
I will gamble, though.
Will I act?
No, no, no, wait.
We're gonna look for a shop first.
No gambling.
Oh, yo, yo, yo.
Ah, what am I doing?
You're not gonna hit me.
Insane precision on my shots today.
I'm like the American sniper.
Except I'm not a sniper and I'm not American either.
But somehow it works out.
I also have fake babies with me.
It all works.
I appreciate that they don't spread their shots like the other ones I met earlier.
You can actually deal with these.
Dodge that ooey.
The knife just took care of him.
No, it's not a real shop.
Maybe he drops an item for me, though.
This would bring me happiness.
Oi.
Just more health.
I mean, money.
Good.
That guy was waiting.
Superball.
He has to fire a bouncing tier.
Ha!
That's a very low chance.
It's not bouncing at all.
Oh, there's one.
Yeah, that's too little chance.
I like being safe from floor stuff.
How safe am I actually with it, though?
Immunity to damage from spikes.
And, I mean, that's just so huge.
That can easily spiral out of control for me, you know?
It's good to be protected.
Oh, there we go.
Flight.
There we go.
Dude, I'm killing it.
Not even a problem.
Gobby's tail.
This is so underwhelming.
Wait, why did I lose so much HP?
I have full HP.
I didn't even get hit during that fight.
What happened?
Huh?
I played perfect.
Why did I?
Okay.
I don't get what just happened.
Like, I didn't get hit once.
But it's okay.
We're gonna find more.
It's no problem.
Ahoy!
You're not gonna beat me!
I am the master of labyrinths.
Solid.
Okay.
Dude, the gravity's affecting my shot.
That's crazy.
Nice.
And we go here.
Wait, actually, this should work.
Wait, I'm immune to this!
Ha ha ha!
Yeah!
Actually, killing it.
There's the boss!
Double trouble!
What does that mean?
Big room, more enemies!
Okay, okay.
Oh god.
This may be bad.
Here, that's for you.
I didn't do anything.
Oh my goodness.
Dude, what the fuck?
This is insane!
One of them is down.
That's huge.
Oi man.
Man, man, man, man, man.
I'm kind of glad I'm hit them now.
Um, wait, uh, this may be a bad idea.
No, wait.
Reduces red heart containers to one.
So this is good!
Yeah, man!
I thought maybe it would just put me down to one in general.
So that, you know, I would have to play really well for a while to build my hearts up again.
But I don't have to.
Wait, maybe I should just move on, actually.
No, actually, clearing these rooms is gonna give me energy.
AKA black hearts.
So this is good.
What is this?
Oh, nothing.
Oh my god.
You can't beat me.
I'm too fast.
Nice.
Oh, yeah.
Sick.
And we get to do this.
Um,
no problem.
No,
I cannot lose.
This is the run, by the way.
Oh god, please, we can do it, right?
And you know what this means?
We can finally move on to the next challenge, if we do this.
I'm totally selling the skin before the bearish shot right now.
I really should stop speaking.
That was an amazing shot.
What's that?
Uh, nah.
That's a good one?
Uh, definitely take that.
Second hand?
Nah.
And take that.
And this one.
Oh, I'm gonna blow you up.
We got the devil for that one.
The sun!
Oh, yeah.
Very nice.
And this one is open as well.
Oi!
I should have seen that coming.
Nice.
More money.
And I think we're done now.
We can move on.
Oh, no, I didn't want that.
Fantastic floor.
Absolutely incredible.
No complaints.
Super happy.
Here we go.
There was nothing else in that room, right?
No, it's a big one.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Oh!
Following familiar... Ooh.
Let me think.
Yeah.
Oh, I could also... Yeah, no, no active.
We're gonna do this.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Moving on.
Now it's time for mom.
Three books?
Well, don't mind if I do.
Let's see what we got here.
Random pickup.
Nice.
Okay.
Bookworm.
Belial.
This is the temporary damage up.
Yes.
But of course, I mean, the Satanic Bible is just goaded.
I need to keep that, no matter what.
Also, the sun.
I forgot what it did other than healing.
Increase my damage, I think, a little bit.
Um, just start gambling like crazy now.
Nobody knows the troubles you have seen.
I know!
So true.
What is that?
Myosotis?
Up to four uncollected pickups from the previous floor will spawn in the starting room of a new floor.
Nah.
I did not miss anything.
Wait, what is that?
Grants an increase to all stats when held.
Active items charged is fully depleted.
Nah, that never happens.
Because I always gain one charge at least with my current setup here.
Dude, what's up with all these trinkets?
Logs can be broken up.
No, I don't need that.
Believe in yourself.
Follow the zebra.
I'm gonna note that down.
Could mean something like black and white.
Follow the zebra, right?
They're black and white.
So if I see something with the pattern of a zebra or something that's black and white, you know, follow the cat.
Wait, we got dogs?
Oh, wait a minute now.
Dog, cat, zebra.
We follow them all.
I shall be stalking all the animals.
In fact, I haven't seen any animals, actually.
Unless it's maybe an enemy?
Apple of... Dude, what's with these trinkets?
50% chance to convert a red heart into a blue spider instead of healing.
Hey, that's good for me.
Unless I had the guy that converts to... What is it called?
I don't have that.
The guy who takes the... Yeah, take this then.
No, I still prefer not taking damage from floor stuff.
I hate floor stuff.
Yeah, the one in the top right is only spawning trinkets and I'm not interested.
Maybe I keep this on while I do this right now.
In case I get red hearts.
Stop with the keys.
I've had enough.
Okay, maybe we save the remaining.
No, I don't...
I missed everything.
Oh yeah, I saw that coming in as soon as they appeared.
Wait, look at this.
No way is not happening, bro.
Nope.
No, no, no, no, no.
Why is it always six?
Have you noticed?
Like, it's always six.
Good.
Blow this up.
I think the black stuff on the floor just slows you down.
Or something like it.
Okay.
This guy can take damage, right?
Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
There's a lot of blue fires here.
This is doable.
Maybe here.
Yeah, yeah.
Whatever.
Okay, now that I have that...
Oh wait, I can... I take no damage.
Shit.
Well, okay then.
That was my last bomb.
I shouldn't have used that.
Oh my god.
Dude, it's no chill.
Okay, let's see what this does.
Fully heals, reveals.
Oh, reveals the map.
Then I'll use it.
Secret discovered.
Sir, we have a pinpoint.
I'm going in.
Come here now.
Good.
Two red hearts.
But look at this.
Oh no, wait, we don't have that item that turns them into flies or whatever it was.
I left it behind.
Oh, I don't have any bombs.
I can grab that one, right?
Okay.
Scary.
Okay, bomb it open.
Dude, I'm drowning in too many hearts.
It's too much of the good stuff.
This is going to be so tough.
How am I doing this?
I'm actually Neo.
Wow!
Oh, shit.
I didn't mean to pick that up.
I was going to save that battery, damn it.
Also, that was a waste.
Let's see here.
Damage range.
That's the same.
Homing.
Okay, let's use that.
Homing shots against mom.
Clean.
Absolutely clean.
That was so good.
And look at that one.
Oh, I'll take that.
No problem.
Right.
Okay, moving on.
Wait, I think I just realized why I lost hearts when I picked up the other item I had.
It's because it cost hearts to pick up.
That must have been it.
It sounds really dumb, but it's actually just that.
Because I looked at my hearts just now.
Wait, wait a minute.
This happened again.
It makes sense.
Okay.
It's not, uh, it lives yet.
We have this little in-betweener.
On the corner.
Okay.
I hate the eyes.
How do you dodge him?
I like, I stare at their eyes and go like, when do I move?
So difficult to do.
Give me black hearts.
Whoa.
Friendship necklace.
Familius orbit around Isaac.
But they already do.
Kinda.
I'm good.
Yeah.
Okay, then.
Hey, I'll take that.
I really need bombs.
Why am I so bomb starved?
And that's it.
Can't even open that chest.
That's so sad.
And there's the boss.
I'm doing it.
Conquest.
There you are.
He's feared.
Fear seems to be really effective against him.
Solid.
That was beautiful.
Absolutely beautiful.
Uh, this one I forget what does, but I'm actually gonna take it.
Yeah, fuck it.
I'm taking it.
Wait, there's also this?
Wait a sec.
Huh.
Oh, I can, I can choose to remove a lot of hearts here.
Wait, so many spikes and this?
Sacrificial altar could actually be nuts.
But then again, guarantees, oh, no, I don't need that.
We're approaching the end.
I'm actually not going to take any of these, but I will take this.
No, it's an active.
Fuck me.
Maybe I can use it on this floor at least.
Now I want to charge my, oh my God.
No.
Oh, well, it's fine.
It's okay.
I mean, we currently have a good setup.
It's fine.
And it's closed.
Why are you closed?
Oh, fuck this.
They did something different.
I thought they were statically moving in the predetermined orientation.
Give me bombs.
So much money.
Nope.
No stepping.
The gravity is pulling in their projectiles.
That's funny.
Yeah.
That's huge.
The tacos.
I can smell them, guys.
You don't have a baby, do you?
You're actually kind of tricky.
I see that you're tricky.
You bastard.
The greatest adversaries myself.
Oh, wow.
Oh, look
at that one.
That is so not necessary or needed right now.
Is that a question?
It's a question mark card.
The devil.
It's not even that exciting.
Are we done?
No, we're not done.
Man, this book is so incredibly good.
It's one of the best actors.
I have a lot of best actors right now.
It's a constantly updating list.
But it's really good.
I don't need that.
Then again, no, I don't need it.
Don't change if it ain't broke, right?
Where's the boss at?
Come on, I'm ready for you.
Uh oh.
I'm actually gonna... no, no, no, no.
Line him up.
Four Colossus.
It lives, not for long.
The eye is confused.
Clean, absolutely clean.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So far, so good.
Wait, am I crazy or is this harder than normal?
I feel like he's harder than normal.
Like he's doing all kinds of shit that he's not normally doing.
Oh, shit, whoa.
Was that clean or what?
That was mega clean.
Brimstone!
We're taking it.
We're taking that.
But wait a sec.
What is the other...
Maybe we'll get three out of three on something.
No, conjoined.
Okay.
We're taking this.
I mean, and Leviathan.
We fly.
Yes.
The tacos.
I'm so happy.
You know what?
I feel so good.
We're gonna go to heaven.
That's right.
Dude, look at that.
Double red and black.
Oh, it's so cool looking.
Oh, that's amazing.
Okay, don't get overexcited.
Stick to the schedule.
Don't be a bitch and start throwing the run.
What's this?
The worst time I could have done it.
It's like I waited for them.
Kill them all.
Oh my god, it's so good.
It's so good.
Brimstone, my beloved.
I'm gonna save that battery.
It's not a full battery.
It's just one of those shitty ones.
Now we do this.
Then we go grab the battery.
Nice.
It's optimal gameplay here.
Just kill everything fast.
That's kind of cool.
Sick.
Why not?
Even better.
I shall... oh wait, I can fly.
Right.
Oh yeah, I don't need...
I'm immune to stuff on the floor now.
I can finally replace it.
That's so nice.
The Empress...
Oh, oh shit.
I thought that was done with soul hearts.
That's okay.
He actually hit me.
Okay, okay.
We gotta calm down a little bit.
That was ice.
I mean, I don't need that.
Whoa!
Hello.
Stop that.
Here we go.
Oh wait, wait.
We're not going to heaven.
Because we're in hell.
Oh, oh shit.
That's fine.
It really should not be a problem.
Want to get that last charge here.
There we go.
Let's go.
Wish me luck.
Precharge.
Here we go.
Satan.
Wake up.
Oh!
Okay, it's fine, it's fine.
We're mega chilling.
Mega chill.
Oh baby!
In my mouth!
What a way to end it.
Beautiful man.
That was a hard challenge.
But honestly, things couldn't have gone better than they did in that run.
That was incredible.
I got everything I needed.
The book that gave me infinite black hearts.
Finish it up with the brimstone at the end.
Oh!
Wow!
Satanic Bible carry for sure.
But also, I played pretty well, I would say, in that one.
Why is the menu music garbled?
Just refresh.
Refresh the stream.
It's a Twitch issue.
Sometimes, you know, you lag behind, and then Twitch tries to compensate by slowing up and shit, and it's not really working well.
Oh man!
That was amazing!
Let me put on something here.
I'll think a little more relaxing.
Because I need to calm down now.
What a run.
It's not even that it was that hard.
You know, the challenge.
It's just a mental thing at this point.
Because I've been failing it so much, you know.
Really wanting to complete it, finally.
And I did.
What kind of tacos are you having?
I'm going to get, well, I haven't bought it yet, but I'm going to go to the store now.
And get, you know, the, not the hard shell tacos, but the other ones, you know, the, what do you call it?
The pancake thingies.
I'm going to get some chicken, some spices, tomatoes, guacamole, or maybe just some whatever, the guacamole is made of.
Red onion, chilies, and that's pretty much it, I guess.
Maybe some, I don't know, something else.
Did I miss something in that?
What else do I need?
I think I got most of it.
I don't like cilantro, so none of that.
Maybe some lime.
Cheese, of course, some cheese would be nice.
Oh yeah, jalapenos, that's a good idea.
Pancake thingies.
Yeah, tortillas, that's the one, exactly.
You know what, GG game, that's a good idea.
I've been wanting to do that for a while.
I just don't know which one to add.
Maybe the one where you pet the cat.
The one, you know, the meme with the cat being pet really, really hard.
And the cat is getting squeezed, you know?
Or squished.
Hey, what's up, meeps kitten?
Yeah, you don't like cilantro either?
Tastes like soap, right?
Apparently it's a very common thing, a lot of people feel that way.
But then there's the other half of the people that love cilantro.
I wish I was one of those, because it looks amazing in food, right?
I want to be able to eat it.
Yeah, it's genetic, it's weird.
Try pastor Anasada.
Is that a food or a religious man?
Because I don't think I want to try him.
I got the soap gene, still love cilantro?
Wow, I guess you just love eating soap.
Interesting.
You just love that taste.
You've never had real tacos?
I don't think I have either, honestly.
Because I haven't been to Mexico or any of those amazing places that serve the original ones.
The closest thing is, you know, buying them from a so-called Mexican place here.
Even though it's not really Mexican.
I've had really good ones, but not true original tacos.
Mexicans don't eat tacos?
Really?
Well, who does?
I've been led astray them.
I thought they loved that stuff.
For good reason.
We do at least twice a day.
Well, there you go.
Okay, so...
Few minutes to analyze secret rooms.
No, what do you mean?
What do you mean by that?
Sweets love tacos?
I think everyone loves tacos.
I mean, it's just a combination of all the best things.
It's really hard not to like them, I guess.
I think he just wants to know what you think while deciding where a secret room could be.
Well, I guess...
Well, don't tell me, of course.
I think...
I don't know.
But the fact that you guys are asking me about it makes me think there's a very clear pattern to it now, you know?
So I guess there is something...
There's a pattern to it.
But I would say...
There's a high chance of it being in between other rooms, you know?
I feel like I see it often when there's like one room missing and there's a circle of rooms around it.
Maybe also at the very edges.
You know, if you have like a very long hallway, I like to look for it there.
But just because it feels right, you know?
That's pretty much it.
Based on the screenshot.
And the screenshot doesn't tell me anything.
Honestly, the screenshot that I took looks like...
Doesn't look like anything to me.
I'm Mexican, there's tacos in every corner, and there's no taco place going bankrupt.
And you probably have it so cheap as well, right?
Like you can probably buy it really...
like really nice tacos for not a lot of money.
That's what I want.
If you go get tacos in Denmark at a taco place, you can expect to pay insane prices for something that isn't really that good.
Unless you find the perfect place.
Like in Copenhagen, something really highly rated.
It's just such a rip-off.
What do you think about the new character?
Oh, good question.
Almost forgot about that.
I think it's interesting and I need to play it more.
I don't know what to think yet.
It's very different from the others, just because you have that extra resource on the left.
So yeah.
The new character is Melancholia.
No, Bethany.
Bethany.
It's Beth.
Yes, let's have it at that.
Oh yeah, screenshot.
I didn't play that much with Bethany yet, but I would love to play more with Bethany.
I don't know why I said Melancholia.
It was something with E as the second letter.
So I was like, ah, it's Melancholia.
But it's Bethany.
Best taco seasoning, garlic, cayenne pepper, salt pepper, lime juice, cumin.
Yeah, true.
Garlic, that's true.
I gotta add that.
The only thing I can't make with tacos at home is something I feel the birria meat.
I just don't know how to do it.
Like, I always do chicken, and then I add like the spices you just mentioned.
It's good, but it's never as good.
I don't know what they do to that meat, you know?
It's just unmatched.
On Doko, you gotta go get tacos now.
You have no option.
You gotta do it.
Everyone gets tacos.
Birria not hard just takes forever.
Yeah, this is a problem, because I'm super lazy when it comes to, you know, making food that takes five hours or so.
Unless it's Christmas food.
I love preparing that for a long time.
It is amazing.
I parked when he bought coupon.
That's good.
The coupon was amazing.
This
is turned into a taco discussion now.
I do like guacamole, yes, thanks.
I try to stream at the same time every time.
Toes gober.
Wait, toes gober?
Oh, man.
I'm both, I don't know, frightened and excited about your name.
They make bath bomb style seasoning balls you can toss in a pressure cooker if you want a cheap birria.
Man, I don't have room for a pressure cooker.
I would love to have stuff like that.
I would also love to have like a rice cooker and stuff, you know, people say it's amazing.
My kitchen is just so tiny.
One of these days in the future, when I really make it and I, you know, I become rich.
I'm gonna buy a place that has a big kitchen where I can have room to make food.
That would be the dream.
I always think that in video games, when I see big kitchens, I'm like, damn, imagine what it would be like.
To have like a kitchen island and more than two tiles of room for preparing food.
I would totally hire someone to just make tacos for me every day.
I mean, I know they're tiny, but if you put them on a, on one of those kitchen tile tops, they're still gonna take up that tile.
You can't really put anything there, you know, even though they're tiny.
Hype train, I don't know what that means.
It's to do with cheering, right?
Thank you, young nut.
And monkey72, toesgobbler has also subscribed.
I appreciate that, toesgobbler.
Gobble of the toes.
You know what else I would do?
I would hire someone to just stand behind me all day and look at me.
So that every time I turn around, I go, fuck, I didn't realize you were there.
Just to keep the heart rate up, you know?
No, I'm kidding.
I would have him behind me and just give me massage all day.
Show the massage all day.
Or use one of those head massage things, you know, with the... with the spokes on it, the metal spokes on the hair.
Oh my God.
Imagine someone just standing there all day and that's his job.
Just massage your head.
Holy shit, that sounds like a dream.
And people say money doesn't make you happy.
Bullshit, they haven't had a dedicated head squishier behind them.
Hey, meepskin, thank you.
Dude, you are racking up.
You are at 235.
You need to...
You don't have to do that, man.
Thank you, but you don't have to.
It's so nice of you.
I appreciate it.
Time to bring out the meepskin story again.
Okay, I'm going to do it every...
No, okay, hold on.
He's an astronaut.
There, I said it.
Boom.
There it is.
I actually tell my friends that...
That, I'm not going to say someone I know, because I don't really know you, right?
But someone that I have talked to is like an astronaut.
I say that, you know?
I think it's so cool.
If there was a taco in Isaac, what do you think it would do?
Oh, it would definitely...
It would make you...
What would the taco do?
Let me think.
Tacos are delicious.
Tacos are healthy.
And they would probably give you two hearts.
You eat a taco, you get two hearts.
Dude, thank you.
That's way too many subs.
What the hell?
Are you made of money or something?
I hope you are.
Thank you very much, man.
Please don't go into debt or something over this.
I mean, he is an astronaut.
Wait, are astronauts rich?
I don't think they are even, which is so sad.
I think the people that went to the moon just now, I don't think they're paid that much money.
Separated by a couple, you know, centimeters of steel or whatever, between you and space, and you get paid a shitty wage.
I mean, yeah, stop saying it's too much, you deserve every single sub.
I feel like I don't.
But I appreciate you saying that.
I mean, at the end of the day, you know, as long as you guys are watching, that's more than enough for me.
And unless you're, you know, super rich or have insane disposable income, then I kind of feel bad about you donating money or giving subs to me when you're already here watching it, right?
Which is already producing money for me.
So that's how I feel about that.
Unless you're like, you know, able to do it and not...
have problems, right?
Definitely not going into debt over this.
Also, I'm not an astronaut by trade.
I just got to go once and paid for it, not vice versa.
That makes you technically an astronaut, though.
But yeah, not by trade, but technically is the best form of correct, right?
The amount of time I spent watching you would have cost way more if it was a movie in a theater, and this is better.
I bet you didn't watch the expedition playthrough, though.
I know you weren't a big fan of that either.
I mean, the best thing you could possibly do if you want to support me is to just, you know, watch the stream and all that.
Leave a comment on YouTube and like videos and stuff.
That is so important.
And that's really all you need to do if you want to support me.
I've been skimming.
I ended it early, unfortunately.
It just wasn't for me.
I was planning on actually continuing, but at the very end, I was like, ah, man.
I have to be true to myself, you know?
I wasn't enjoying it as much as I thought I was going to.
But yeah, sometimes that happens.
I mean, I've had that happen with Terraria as well, right?
Also a very well-liked game by the community.
Overwhelmingly positive on Steam and it just didn't vibe with me.
I was going to ask you to pick side in the game of the year debates.
There's no need now.
Yeah, there's no need.
You know why?
Because it's Blue Prince, in my opinion.
I mean, Silksong was fantastic.
And I actually think Silksong was better than the original Hollow Knight simply because the combat was so incredibly fun.
I had such a blast.
Like, I was just enjoying myself so much playing Silksong, you know?
But Blue Prince was just something else, man.
It is so innovative.
I've never played anything like it.
It was so addictive.
Such a cool game.
The music was great.
Fucking fantastic game.
But I haven't played more than those games, right?
So maybe there's other games that, you know, could have taken over that.
Depending on how good it was.
But yeah, I haven't played any others.
From that year.
Opposite for you?
Oh, you're talking to someone else, sorry.
You still haven't played Blue Prince?
Well, let me ask you this third share.
Do you like puzzle games?
And do you like roguelikes?
And if you say yes to those two, you're most likely gonna like Blue Prince.
That's what I would say.
Although, more puzzle.
If you like puzzles, that's probably the bigger question.
How is Isaac for me?
Very addicting.
If you can't tell.
I've been streaming it three days in a row now.
Which is kind of unusual for me.
That's Stranding 2 I'm looking forward to as well.
And it actually just came out on PC.
So, you know, soon time, I think.
I was waiting for that to come out on PC.
It is definitely virtual crack.
And I think it may be a mistake for me to start playing...
I was planning on this.
Factorio next.
Or at the same time.
That may just be too much crack at the same time.
Because I have played some Factorio and trust me, I was cracked up for that short period.
I know I'm gonna fall into a deep rabbit hole with that game if I actually commit to it and play it properly.
Would I survive?
Would I die from that?
Thanks for the sub, young nut.
I earned a hype chest.
I'm gonna open that.
Spit the truth emote.
Sick.
I got an emote.
If you ever get tired of Isaac, Mutagenix will light your fire.
I know.
People have been saying that one is the one to play.
If you like Isaac.
Because it's the same creator.
It's the same...
Not same type of game, but you know, it's the same vibe, I guess.
The addicting style of it.
Tamble lane!
Thank you!
Holy shit, you guys are gifting so many subs.
What the hell?
Wait a minute.
Where's that photo of Jackie on Discord?
With the karate kick.
Yeah, Talos too is also on the back burner.
Thank you, Tamble Lane.
And it's so cool to see a bunch of new people in here that I haven't seen before either.
Have some of you found this dream through Twitch recommended for Isaac?
I wonder how much that actually does for Discovery.
If I'm actually finding new viewers through that.
You did Robson?
Oh, look, first time chatters there.
Nice.
Okay, that's cool.
The way he's actually good at bullet hells.
Oh, thank you.
Because I really don't consider myself as a person good at that.
But I guess, you know, learning is taking place.
If you played enough, you start to learn.
IRL blind playthrough soon.
I'm doing that right now.
I've been doing it ever since I was born.
Recently, I learned to do taxes properly for the first time.
And actually have fun.
I like doing my taxes.
I may be a freak.
A big.
Your parents didn't give you any hints on life.
Well, they did.
And that's how I learned it.
At least some of it.
My dad, especially.
Every time I don't know how to do anything, you know, adult, I call my dad.
What do I do now?
How old are you?
I'm 34.
I'm an old man.
Well, not that old, but I'm soon 40.
That feels old to me.
Your dad spoiled you on the playthrough.
I guess that's so funny.
Like don't walk across the street when cars are coming.
Don't spoil it, man.
Let me figure out on my own.
I thought you were Gen C.
I don't know what that means.
Like when is Gen C?
What year is that?
Gen C, is that 2000 or?
No, that's no.
Yeah, it's 2000, right?
2000 people.
No, yeah, I'm 1992.
So whatever that is.
I'm not a boomer either, right?
What am I?
Millennial.
Okay.
See, I would think 2000 would be millennial.
Isn't that a millennium?
When you round a thousand?
Confusing.
It's like when people say the 21st century.
That's what we're in now.
Should it be the 20th century?
So confusing.
Do your parents watch the stream sometimes?
No.
At least I don't think so.
There's no way.
They're not just not into the gaming thing.
Millennial is before the millennium.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, 21st century is now.
Exactly.
That's confusing to me.
To me, that's like 2100 and more, right?
You start counting at zero or one.
I start counting at one.
No, I guess I start at zero and then I go to one.
Because I go, this is my baseline.
Then I go one apple.
I don't say zero apple, right?
So technically, I start at zero.
Bro thinks we started at year 100.
Let me think about that.
Does that make sense what you just said?
No, I'm not understanding that.
It's like with family members.
I don't know what an uncle is.
Actually, I do know that because I'm an uncle.
But all the others, I don't.
It's just something I will never learn.
Some people have trouble with the left and right, which I find insane.
Like, I've never had trouble with that, right?
I'm terrible at months as well.
Nowadays, I'm getting better at it, you know?
But I have to sort of...
I have to make up the rhyme, you know?
January, February, March, and so on and so on.
I can't just say, oh, what is the seventh month?
No clue.
I know all the months, and I can do it if I say them in the row, right?
Or in the right order.
But if you...
What is the 11th month?
I don't know.
Okay, that one I know in November, but...
Same.
Over there you go.
I'm not the only one.
Good.
It's tough.
Some people have issues with pictures also.
True.
It's the worst, yeah.
Weekdays I have no problem with, though.
I'm good at weekdays.
I know my weekdays.
Especially Friday.
I know Friday very well.
I was saying, big elephants can add up sums easily to spell until I was like 16.
Wait, what?
Big elephants can add up some...
What does that even mean?
Is that related to months?
No, right?
Okay, you're talking about something else.
To spell the word because.
Oh!
Oh, I see!
To spell because.
I thought you meant to spell.
And then because...
That confused me.
I get it.
I used to say OB a fine girl and kiss me.
For OB AF GKM type stars.
Because there's different types of stars, you know.
O stars all the way down to, you know.
So that's the one I would use.
Although lately I've been saying OB AF GKM.
And that works just as well.
OB AF GKM.
OB AF JKM, yeah.
I feel like it's faster than saying the other one.
Except, yeah, OB AF GKM.
That's it.
Cardinal directions.
I'm so good at it.
I'm pretty much a weather vane.
I'm just not good at, you know, navigating from that.
I can go through my town 10,000 times and I will always need Google Maps.
And I think I can blame Google Maps for that.
If I didn't have Google Maps, I would probably be forced to learn Landmarks.
So I blame all the technology we have, you know.
I really should stop becoming so dependent on it.
IRL mapping.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm always so impressed at those people in the times long gone.
That would draw these incredible looking maps.
Like back then, how would you even know?
Okay, you can walk along a shoreline, right?
But how do you get the dimensions right?
It seems like an insanely hard challenge.
It's unreal.
And they were so close as well.
If you look at satellite images compared to the old maps, it's really impressive.
Blown away by that.
I have not started the second game yet, dead end.
But I'm doing it either tomorrow or the day after.
And I'm deciding between a couple things.
I just don't want to reveal what it is yet in case I end up hating it.
Do you make any common Danish grammar mistakes like missing present tense R?
Danish grammar mistakes.
I don't think so.
I don't actually use Danish too much in my life.
Even my friends I have here are mostly foreigners.
I have a couple Danish friends, but yeah.
I actually don't remember Meep's Kitten.
Let me think.
I've been quite fortunate.
Most of the games I've played, I have actually ended up enjoying quite a bit.
It's actually pretty rare that I ended up playing a game I don't like.
Mostly because I know what games I like, right?
So looking at a game, I can almost immediately tell whether or not I'm gonna like it.
Not always though, but mostly.
And there was one game.
What was that?
Played one game.
I can't even think of it now.
I learned English when I was like 10 probably.
Maybe before that.
I mean, we learned it in school here.
And watching American TV shows, playing games, it's just natural to learn English here.
Because nothing is in Danish here really.
Maybe kids shows, you know, on TV.
But movies and stuff, they're not in Danish unless it's Danish movies.
I
can see the merit in E33, right?
It's just not a game I enjoy very much.
That's all.
Just that the gameplay loop wasn't really me.
It didn't really land for me.
But I can see how it's a good game, you know, to a lot of people.
I can see that.
Yeah, Drog is so good, Yudhry.
The final scene is...
And it's not because it's on Danish, you know, on Denmark.
But that final scene is legitimately so good.
Freaking love it.
Yeah, it really is perfection.
I saw an interview with Guillermo del Toro.
He was just sitting there together with Thomas Winterberg.
And he was saying...
He was pretty much just praising...
He was glazing that movie so hard.
He was fanboying to Thomas Winterberg, which is just so funny to me, you know?
Because Guillermo del Toro is kind of a huge deal in the movie world.
And he was just sitting there going, Oh my God, I can't believe how good that was.
I'm like blown away.
It was so funny to watch.
Yeah.
He's a massive fan of that scene.
In particular, and the movie.
Mughanix will change it.
Don't say...
Dude, you're making me want to play it already.
I got to start or finish Isaac first, you know?
Too much crack is no good.
What if I'm going to end up hating Mughanix, though?
Do you think there's a chance I could end up hating that game, even though I like Isaac?
Could I hate it?
And be honest now, don't be, you know...
You doubt I'll like it?
Ooh, okay.
Spicy.
What do you define as finishing?
I don't know, like...
I would say playing the game for so long that you, like, or for the amount of time and enjoying it through the whole time.
And then stopping when you just don't want to play it anymore.
I guess that would be completing the game for me.
If I stop playing a game because, like, I'm not having...
Yeah, I don't know, it's a hard question to answer, actually.
Because you clearly can't say credits in games like Isaac, right?
That one isn't really gonna fly.
And you can't really say all achievements either, because that's kind of nuts.
So, I don't know.
It's like a blueprint.
It's also hard to define when you've completed that game, you know?
Because, yeah, I don't want to say too much.
Otherwise, I'm going to spoil things, and yeah.
It's more than 50% possible, okay.
Well, in any case, I'm going to be streaming Mugenics.
So, you know, if I end up hating it, you're going to see the whole process.
It's not going to be a recorded game, I don't think.
Oh no, I love the soundtrack from E33.
That was the best part of the game, for sure.
There are so many bangers in that.
And I probably haven't even heard all of them, right?
I think E33 could make an amazing movie.
Like, I would watch the shit out of a movie.
If they ever make one.
Have you been recording these Isaac streams, or is it just...
Wait, what do you mean?
Oh, I see what you mean.
No, no, I'm recording at the same time locally while I'm streaming.
So, the local recording is in 4K.
I put that on YouTube for much better quality.
Yes, I see what you mean now.
They are making one?
Well, there you go.
I'm going to be watching that.
Streams or AI generated?
That would be so impressive though, right?
Wouldn't you be impressed if this was all AI from the start?
Like, that would be next level.
If this truly was AI generated, then we're all cooked.
And it's all...
And my job is gone, I guess.
I'd hope AI would play better.
No, but it's doing it on purpose, so you don't trust or think it's AI, right?
Think about it like this.
An AI would probably realize that a healthy balance of rage bait and good skills is what keeps people watching, you know?
Because it's like rage bait, which makes people mad, so they stay around and write angry comments.
But then the highlights happen, right?
I don't know.
I can imagine that being a thing that AI would optimize for in some way.
Engagement is key.
Yeah, exactly.
I think I'm going to do voice reveal at 500,000 subs.
I'm not going to reveal my real voice yet, of course.
Come on.
This is my real voice.
I mean, okay, there's a couple of, you know, filters on OBS, but that's pretty much it.
There's a voice gate, and I have a compressor on, a very light one.
That's pretty much it.
I don't use, you know, filters to change my voice.
I just don't do that.
That's not something I would do, okay?
Anyway, guys, I'm going.
I need to go to the store and grab some supplies and make my tacos, because I'm starving.
Yep.
I'm going to be crunching on those while Jackie's going to be crunching on her food.
Thank you for watching, everybody, and thank you for gifting out the subs and staying around, chatting, just hanging out.
I love it.
You guys are so cool.
Making this dream a reality here.
And, you know, fueling my addiction, so yeah.
Thank you.
I'll see you around.